<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Overwatch PC Updates</title>
  <id>https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
  <updated>2018-07-24T12:01:27-07:00</updated>
  <subtitle>Patch notes and updates for Overwatch</subtitle>
  <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/"></link>
  <author>
    <name>Blizzard</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Patch 1.26.0.3</title>
    <updated>2018-07-24T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-07-24:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html"></content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-49154"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Patch 1.25.0.1</title>
    <updated>2018-06-26T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-06-26:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re super excited about this patch because we are adding some social features that we hope you guys really like!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, our Endorsement system. Endorsements give you a way to acknowledge other players for having a positive impact on your gaming experience. We have ways to report people for poor conduct, but now, if you have teammates who coordinated well, a leader who gave great direction, or even someone who was just being positive you can now let them know how much you appreciated it with an endorsement!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Second is Looking for Group. A long-awaited feature that we’ve being dying to get in the game. Looking for group allows you to find like-minded players before you queue to make sure you have the kind of Overwatch experience you want! Things like specifying what game mode want to play, preferring voice chat, and knowing that a player wants to play a certain role before you go into battle together goes a long way toward solid hero compositions and team work. One small tip: Once you have created a LFG group you can browse the list and search for groups that meet your needs and invite them to join up! This is a more proactive approach to getting a group together faster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We can’t wait for you guys to start using these systems!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;—Jeremy Craig, Principal Game Designer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Endorsements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/tm/TMGNJRTM03J01529962538076.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Acknowledge your fellow Overwatch players’ positivity with &lt;a href=&#34;http://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/endorsements/&#34;&gt;endorsements&lt;/a&gt;! Recognize commendable behavior for players exhibiting sportsmanship, being a good teammate, or for shot calling. Commend players who lead you to victory, put the team’s needs above their own, or exhibit humility in victory or grace in defeat. Endorsements are readily available to view on Career Profiles, the Groups menu, and more so you can tell at a glance the types of players you’re playing with. Those who consistently maintain a high endorsement level will receive periodic rewards, while those who display negative behavior or accrue suspensions will lose their endorsements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Looking for Group&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/3g/3GQ8V2FMBVAP1529962572415.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Play your way using the Looking for Group feature! You can control your gameplay experience before stepping into a match by using specific parameters to create your dream team. Join a team of other like-minded players or lead a group of your own by creating a group with your personal preferences such as game mode, role enforcement, and more. Those who want to queue up for Quick Play, Play vs AI, or any competitive mode can set the types of roles others can play. These specifications will then be activated in-game (e.g. players who chose a support role will be restricted to only using heroes in that category).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;GENERAL UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments:&lt;/strong&gt; &#34;Since the line between Offense and Defense heroes has become increasingly blurred, we’ve decided to group all those heroes into a single new “Damage” category. We believe that the term more closely matches the role name that is now being used in Overwatch League and across most of the game’s community.&#34;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;All heroes in the Defense and Offense categories have been merged into a new category: Damage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Combat can now be heard 25% further away&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Changed the name of the Varok spray to Saurfang&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[PC] Players must have Blizzard SMS Protect enabled on their account to be eligible for the Top 500&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Acknowledge and Interact buttons are now separate input bindings&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Career Profile&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added an Inspire Uptime Percentage statistic for Brigitte on the Career Profile&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Removed some statistics for Symmetra on the Career Profile&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added a Scoped Critical Hit Accuracy statistic for Widowmaker on the Career Profile&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Career Profiles will no longer be public by default (now defaults to Friends Only). An option to make Career Profiles visible has been added under Options &amp;gt; Social &amp;gt; Profile Visibility&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;ARCADE UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Symmetra can now be played in 1v1 duel game modes (e.g. 1v1 Limited Duel and 1v1 Mystery Duel)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Doomfist&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/7c/7C4LVDIF8ZX21529967875652.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; The increased movement speed on Meteor Strike gives Doomfist new options in how and where to deploy it. His passive is also being increased, allowing him to survive more often when diving into enemies.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Meteor Strike&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Bonus movement speed increased from 150% to 200%&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;The Best Defense…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Shield gain increased from 30 to 35 for normal abilities&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;McCree&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/kv/KVBH6MG8C5N91529967905889.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; While McCree’s Deadeye rarely came into play at 70 meters, we are increasing the range so it cannot be a limiting factor during normal gameplay.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Deadeye&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Range increased from 70 meters to 200 meters&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Orisa&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/3f/3FE4LV1S3UGO1529967929720.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; Supercharger wasn’t getting enough use, considering its impact. This change allows Orisa to use her ultimate more aggressively, knowing that she will be able to generate them more easily.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Supercharger&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ultimate cost reduced by 15%&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Symmetra&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/pt/PT31K4K5FMTD1529967943098.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; The goal of these changes is to move Symmetra to her new damage role and make her more flexible and viable across more areas of the game than she was previously. Now that Symmetra is no longer a support hero, she is expected to be able to dish out heavy damage, and these changes allow for her to do so. She should be more powerful and interesting in more team compositions and maps, and she should also be stronger on offense and defense.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Photon Projector&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No longer locks onto targets&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Range increased to 10 meters&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Damage ramping now takes 2 seconds per damage level instead of 1 second&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Damage ramp increased from 30/60/120 to 60/120/180&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now generates ammo instead of spending it when hitting a barrier&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ammo reduced from 100 to 70&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Alternate Fire&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No longer pierces targets&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now explodes on contact&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Projectile speed increased&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Charge up speed increased&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Damage changed to 60 impact / 60 explosive&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Sentry Turret&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Turret is now placed like a projectile instead of being set in place&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Can hold a max of 3, down from 6&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Can now deploy a max 3, down from 6&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Damage increased&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Amount of slowing effect increased&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Teleporter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Can now place the exit up to 25 meters away from Symmetra&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Entrance will automatically be built in front of Symmetra, rather than at her team’s spawn point&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lasts 10 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Health lowered to 300&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;More things can teleport through it (e.g. Junkrat’s RIP-Tire)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Entrance can be destroyed&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If either the entrance or exit is destroyed, the other is removed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;New Ultimate: Photon Barrier&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Deploys a barrier that is big enough to span and cut through an entire map&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Orientation can be changed by pressing the ultimate button again&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lasts 15 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Has 5000 health&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;MAP UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Horizon Lunar Colony&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments:&lt;/strong&gt; We’ve wanted to make some gameplay improvements to Horizon Lunar Colony for some time now. The defenders’ spawn room had a problem with its main exit that allowed defenders to quickly duck back inside and regain health while attackers shot at them without doing damage. Since we were already reworking the entire back area, we decided to make some more changes addressing player feedback. The idea behind the rework of Point A was to not only help the defenders a bit, but also provide some gameplay options aside from sitting on the point and trying to hold it for as long as possible. Easier access to high ground, as well as limiting the routes for attackers (or at least allowing for defenders to more easily spot the attackers), will allow more opportunity for counters and create a better gameplay experience.&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ve made a lot of additions and changes to the art throughout the map for you to discover as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point A&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added a staircase on the right when exiting the Hydroponics Room&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Removed the door to the lower room on the right&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Removed the small wall on the catwalk above Point A&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added some cover walls to the catwalk area&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Moved the door next to the staircase that led to Winston’s room&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The door is now on the side of the wall in the training pit&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Moved the large health pack to the back of the room&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Removed some clutter in the upper left computer room&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hydroponics Room&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Switched the positions of the large and small health pack&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Changed some of the hydroponic plant cover on the right&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point B&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Defender spawn room exits moved from the front to the sides out of direct line of fire&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Small rooms added at spawn room exits&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Additional cover added near the spawn room exits&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added a route and larger platform leading to the back right corner&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Raised the platform to the same height as the attackers’ platform on the opposite side of the point&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The location of the old defender exit is now an alcove with a small health pack&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Both teams can still pass behind the point, but there is now a cut-through in the middle of the wall for better access&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The area above the window overlooking the point is now covered&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A large platform with cover has been attached to the left side of the catwalk&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The upper platform for the attackers has been reduced&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The doorway leading to the platform is slightly smaller&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;June26_General_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;June26_General_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented loading screens from displaying the game mode&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the capture point UI to display capture progress as 100% before the point was captured&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused some sprays to be pixelated&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;June26_ai_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;AI&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;June26_ai_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Sombra bot to continue hacking health packs if the ability was disabled in a Custom Game&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;June26_heroes_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Heroes&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;June26_heroes_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ana&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Ana’s Naptime achievement from being granted when interrupting Moira’s Coalescence&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Ana’s Sleep Dart effect to persist on afflicted targets after changing heroes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bastion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented McCree’s Flashbang from interrupting Bastion’s Configuration: Tank transformation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Bastion’s treads to disfigure if he was frozen while in Tank configuration&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brigitte&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Junkrat’s grenades to damage Brigitte when hitting her Barrier Shield&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Brigitte’s Barrier Shield to become indestructible if her Barrier Shield Cooldown Time modifier was set to 0% in a Custom Game&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Brigitte’s Rocket Flail to clip into the ground during her Flail highlight intro on King’s Row&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Brigitte to proc Inspire when hitting gondola omnics with her Rocket Flail in Rialto&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Brigitte to proc Inspire by hitting the motorcycle in the Junkertown attacker spawn room&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Brigitte to use Shield Bash while affected by Steel Trap or Graviton Surge&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Brigitte’s Inspire passive from sometimes healing allies out of line of sight&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Brigitte’s knee pad and foot to clip the ground during her Kneel victory pose when wearing her Paladin or Engineer skins&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Brigitte’s arm animation to shake when using Repair Pack and Rally in quick succession&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doomfist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Meteor Strike animation to place him back on the ground when used in midair&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Meteor Strike cooldown UI from being hidden if he died during its activation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the HUD messaging for Doomfist’s Meteor Strike to indicate that players can zoom their camera out&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Rocket Punch from dealing bonus damage when the target hit a friendly Mei’s Ice Wall&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Doomfist’s Rocket Punch bonus damage to hit Genji after using Swift Strike to move through the punch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Rocket Punch’s bonus damage from applying if the enemy used an evasive ability at the same time they hit a wall (e.g. Moira’s Fade, Tracer’s Blink, or Reaper’s Wraith Form)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented Doomfist’s Rocket Punch from impacting some walls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Rocket Punch, Rising Uppercut, and Seismic Slam from not playing the appropriate sound effect if these abilities were disabled or on cooldown&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented enemies struck by Doomfist’s Rocket Punch from taking additional collision damage when hitting Mei’s Cryo-freeze&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Rising Uppercut animation from playing when used after hitting something with Rocket Punch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Doomfist to use Seismic Slam and escape Graviton Surge when within range&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s failed Seismic Slams to display the wrong UI information&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Seismic Slam from being usable if spammed in a Custom Game with 0% cooldown modifier&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;D.Va&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused D.Va’s mech to do a standing pose right before detonating&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug prevented the South Korean flag decal from displaying when she was in her mech&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug prevented projectiles from hitting D.Va if she stood behind her mech after it detonated&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the Team Kill sound effects from playing for D.Va inside her mech&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed pilot D.Va could summon extra, empty mechs if she used Call Mech while standing on top of an enemy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed D.Va to activate her mech boosters after activating her Self-Destruct&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Genji&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Genji’s Swift Strike to do damage after he dies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented stuns from applying if Genji used Swift Strike&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Genji to wall climb while using emotes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hanzo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[PS4] Fixed a bug that prevented Hanzo’s belt tassels from animating with his Young Hanzo or Young Master skin equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Hanzo’s Storm Bow projectiles to sometimes use the sound effect for Storm Arrow&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Hanzo to wall climb while using emotes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Hanzo’s Dragon Strike animation from playing if he was in a Graviton Surge&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junkrat&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Junkrat to place multiple Steel Traps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Junkrat’s projectiles to become invisible if they were shot through railings&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the medal in Junkrat’s Medal victory pose to clip through his chin with his Scarecrow or Hayseed skins equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused turrets to target Junkrat’s Concussion Mines while airborne&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lúcio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Lúcio from using his Sonic Amplifier when waving hello&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Lucio from using Soundwave if he had zero ammo&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;McCree&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented McCree’s Flashbang from giving credit for environmental kills&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused McCree’s Deadeye targeting markers to persist if the target died while it was active&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused McCree’s Deadeye reticle to lock onto players who die while the ability was active&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the tumbleweed from appearing in McCree’s The Duel highlight intro&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mei&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Mei from receiving environmental kill credit if her targets were frozen&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mei’s projectiles to appear that they weren’t passing through friendly barriers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mercy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Mercy’s Caduceus Blaster and Caduceus Staff from appearing when switching between weapons and using quick melee at the same time&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mercy’s Caduceus Blaster shots to become invisible if they were deflected by Genji if her Pink skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Mercy’s Guardian Angel cooldown from resetting if Valkyrie was used midflight&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the cooldown on Mercy’s Guardian Angel from being refunded while Valkyrie was active&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the resolution quality of Mercy’s Today’s Top 5 highlights icon to drop with her Zhuque skin equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented player names from displaying when being healed by Mercy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Mercy to see her eliminated teammates while resurrecting a target&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Mercy to switch weapons while using her Caduceus emote&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moira&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Moira’s Biotic Grasp from damaging barriers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Moira’s Biotic Grasp’s beam to disappear when attaching to barriers from certain angles&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from receiving the Excuse Me achievement when successfully interrupting Moira’s Coalescence&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Moira’s Biotic Grasp to heal targets behind an enemy barrier&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Moira’s Biotic Orb to pass through breakable objects&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Moira’s Biotic Grasp to attach onto the base of targets (e.g. Mei’s Cryo-freeze)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Orisa&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from being awarded Orisa’s Halt State achievement&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Orisa’s Fusion Driver from closing if her Halt projectile was affected by Defense Matrix or Deflect immediately after it spawned&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug where Orisa’s arm would clip into her leg during her Puppy emote&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the effect of Orisa’s Halt! to persist if Wraith Form or Fade were used immediately after being pulled in&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pharah&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Pharah from being knocked back by her Concussive Blast in spawn rooms&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reaper&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug with Reaper’s Shadow Step sound effect continuously playing while moving around on breakable terrain in Petra.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reinhardt&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Reinhardt’s Barrier Field from not playing the correct sound effect if it was affected by Sombra’s Hack&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Reinhardt’s Barrier Field cooldown to cancel an active hammer swing when it became ready to use&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Reinhardt’s Rocket Hammer eliminations from receiving credit in the Kill Feed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reaper&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug with Reaper’s Shadow Step sound effect continuously playing while moving around on breakable terrain in Petra&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Roadhog&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Roadhog’s Chain Hook to reel in targets even if the ability was interrupted&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sombra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Sombra’s Hack from interrupting Symmetra’s Teleporter placement&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug caused Sombra’s Hack to be interrupted by thin environment objects (e.g. lamp posts)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Sombra’s Translocator from being destroyed when it was thrown off a level&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Symmetra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s Photon Barrier from blocking Reinhardt’s Earthshatter&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Symmetra’s Photon Projector to gain charge when used on breakable objects&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s Photon Barrier from being placed with the correct orientation if the player rapidly turned during its placement&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s Photon Barrier from being placed on moving platforms or payloads&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Symmetra to place her Shield Generator inside gates on certain maps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Symmetra to place her Sentry Turrets inside chests and vending machines&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Symmetra’s Sentry Turrets to deploy at maximum range without sticking to a surface&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s Sentry Turrets from dealing the correct amount of damage and slow values&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Symmetra’s Teleporter to self-destruct when it was placed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Torbjörn’s turret from being built on Symmetra’s Teleporter&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s secondary fire from consuming ammo when minimally charged&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s Teleporter from teleporting allies that moved through it at high movement speeds (e.g. Genji’s Swift Strike)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Symmetra’s Teleporter to fall through the ground if placed on platform edges&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s eyes from aligning properly during her Askew and Snowflakes highlight intros with her Dragon skin equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Torbjörn&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Torbjörn’s Batter Up emote from playing sound effects if he switched weapons&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tracer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Tracer’s Pulse Bomb to stick on the opposite side of barriers when thrown at a certain angle&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Tracer’s animation to pause at the start of her Bomb Spin emote&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Widowmaker&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Widowmaker’s shooting animation to become stuck if she scoped while firing and then jumped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug with the grammar in the flavor text for Widowmaker’s Comtesse skin&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Widowmaker’s Venom Mine from being destroyed when thrown over the environment edges on Oasis Gardens&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winston&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug where placing Winston’s Barrier Projector while going a step upwards would cause it to fall through the floor&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zenyatta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Zenyatta’s Discord Orb sound effects from playing with his Cultist skin equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Zenyatta’s arm to clip through his pants during his Heroic highlight intro&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;June26_maps_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Maps&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;June26_maps_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blizzard World&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Soldier: 76’s Helix Rockets and Zarya’s primary fire from popping balloons&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Horizon Lunar Colony&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused armor packs to land behind crates and not be usable&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Petra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented ability indicators for Seismic Slam and Ice Wall from being visible on the breakable terrain in Petra&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Reinhardt’s Earthshatter to travel across holes in the breakable tile floor on Petra&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rialto&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug where heroes would move left and right on their own while standing in one of the speed boats in the canal&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug where players were able to apply a spray on the surface of a body of water&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watchpoint: Gibralter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the first Attacker spawn room to extend past its walls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-47946"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Patch 1.24.1.1</title>
    <updated>2018-06-14T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-06-14:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://us.forums.blizzard.com/en/overwatch/c/general-discussion&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;https://us.forums.blizzard.com/en/overwatch/c/bug-report&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;https://us.forums.blizzard.com/en/overwatch/c/technical-support&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;&lt;br/&gt;&#xA; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;ARCADE UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Deathmatch&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Increased Deathmatch AFK timer from 60 seconds to 120 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;May22_General_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;May22_General_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Career Profile statistics to clip beneath player names in the Groups tab in the Social menu&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;May22_General_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Mei&#39;s Snowball Offensive&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;May22_General_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mei&#39;s Snowball Blaster reload and Flurry UIs to appear on all players&#39; screens&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-47552"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Patch 1.24.0.1</title>
    <updated>2018-06-05T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-06-05:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://us.forums.blizzard.com/en/overwatch/c/general-discussion&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;https://us.forums.blizzard.com/en/overwatch/c/bug-report&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;https://us.forums.blizzard.com/en/overwatch/c/technical-support&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;ARCADE UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deathmatch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Increased Deathmatch AFK timer from 60 seconds to 120 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mei’s Snowball Offensive&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mei’s Snowball Blaster reload and Flurry UIs to appear on all players’ screens&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-47452"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Patch 1.24.0.1</title>
    <updated>2018-05-22T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-05-22:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;New Seasonal Event: Overwatch Anniversary 2018&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Celebrate Overwatch’s two-year anniversary with a new FFA (free-for-all) Deathmatch map—Petra—and more than 190 Anniversary items (60+ new for 2018), including eight legendary skins: Stealth Bastion, Shieldmaiden Brigitte, Formal Doomfist, Buccaneer Junkrat, Sherlock McCree, Forest Spirit Orisa, Magician Symmetra, and Cybjörn Torbjörn. Did you miss an item from a previous event? Throughout Overwatch Anniversary, you’ll be able to unlock items from past seasonal events with credits (and opening Anniversary Loot Boxes)!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many of our past seasonal brawls will be available to play in the Arcade, and the brawl of the day will rotate throughout the event.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a bonus this year, each Anniversary Loot Box can contain items from past seasonal events! You’ll also get one Legendary Anniversary Loot Box, with at least one guaranteed legendary item, just for logging in to the game during the event.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you all so much for spending the last two years playing Overwatch with us, and we look forward to celebrating with you in-game!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;New Map: Petra&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A group of archaeologists have begun an excavation and preservation project among the ruins of Petra, a new FFA (free-for-all) Deathmatch map that puts all heroes on their own, facing off against one another until one hero scores enough eliminations to win the match.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Take in Petra’s majestic views, from high vistas to twisting passageways and deep caverns. Travel along deadly cliffs, but be careful to not fall off! A dilapidated bridge stretches across the map, and the ground underneath it can crumble away into a lethal pit (with a little firepower). Hopping on a green jump pad will boost you up to Petra’s higher levels and unlock new strategic possibilities for you. . . .&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;New Competitive Play mode: FFA Deathmatch&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Petra and Château Guillard will also be available in an optional Competitive FFA Deathmatch mode with placement matches, skill rating, leaderboards, and the opportunity to earn competitive points.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Ana&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/xl/XL6RBC3KRLAQ1527630418946.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; These changes should help Ana when she is trying to land clutch heals in the middle of a big fight. Allies that do not need healing will no longer block shots meant for allies that do. Increasing her magazine size makes it less likely to be forced into a reload in the middle of an important fight.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;ana&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Biotic Rifle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Projectiles will now pass through allies with full health&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ammo increased from 10 to 14&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Brigitte&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/bw/BWLZGE8PVBJI1527630462150.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; Brigitte’s ultimate is very powerful, especially when it is placed on the entire team. This change will reduce the maximum armor value of Rally, but does not reduce the overall amount of armor given by the ability over its duration. This means when used in combat while her allies are taking damage, it should feel about the same, but the lingering effects of the armor should have less of an impact. Her Shield Bash is a very strong ability on a fairly short cooldown, making it difficult for her opponents to play around. Increasing this cooldown allows for more options when battling against her.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;brigitte&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Rally&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Maximum armor per player reduced from 150 to 100&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;brigitte&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Shield Bash&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cooldown increased from 5 to 6 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Hanzo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/xg/XGT5GAJ80Y7J1527630505280.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; Hanzo’s Storm Arrows are doing too much damage considering his other changes, such as Lunge and projectile speed. This damage reduction will give Hanzo’s enemies a more reasonable chance to react and fight against him while using Storm Arrows.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;hanzo&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Storm Arrows&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Damage reduced from 80 to 70&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;COMPETITIVE PLAY UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Rialto&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Rialto is now available in Competitive Play&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;GAME BROWSER AND CUSTOM GAMES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added Infinite Ultimate Duration and Scalable Ultimate Duration options for Moira’s Coalescence&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;FFA Deathmatch&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ana can now Nano Boost herself&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;May22_General_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;May22_General_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused players to repeatedly return to the Hero Select screen when backfilling into a match&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[PS4/XB1] Fixed a bug that allowed the Show Network Ping to still display as an option under Show Network Stats in the Video tab&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the sound wave visual effect from animating when previewing a voice line unlocked from a loot box&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused a visual error to display 0/0 unlocks on the main menu&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Widowmaker to become stuck in a pillar in the Practice Range&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the Groups tab in the Social menu from dynamically refreshing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes prevented shields from blocking projectiles (e.g. Tracer&#39;s Pulse Bomb and Junkrat&#39;s grenades)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the camera to dip down for a frame when crouching and returning to an upright position&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;May22_ffa_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;FFA Deathmatch&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;May22_ffa_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed groups to queue for Deathmatch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Sombra to be revealed to all enemies if targeted by Hanzo&#39;s Sonic Arrow or Widowmaker&#39;s Infra-sight while stealthed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;May22_gbcg_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Game Browser and Custom Games&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;May22_gbcg_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Moira&#39;s Coalescence&#39;s animation to incorrectly loop when Ultimate Duration was set above 100%&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Moira&#39;s Coalescence SFX to stop playing after a couple of seconds when Ultimate Duration was set above 100%&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused players who were idle in Assault and Skirmish game modes to be flagged as inactive and removed from the match&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented spawn resets and round start dialogue from playing when Random Heroes was enabled&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the start of match dialogue to say &#34;Capture the enemy flag&#34; instead of &#34;Fight&#34; in Team Deathmatch &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused suicides to count as multiple deaths in Deathmatch when the Respawn as Random Hero option was enabled&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;May22_highlights_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Highlights&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;May22_highlights_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused dialogue lines to get cut short at the end of highlights&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused placement indicators to appear red in Play of the Game playbacks and highlights when they were placed on valid ground&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;May22_heroes_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Heroes&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;May22_heroes_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ana&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Ana&#39;s Biotic Rifle crosshair to disappear momentarily when scoping and unscoping&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bastion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug causing Bastion&#39;s Dune Buggy skin textures to stretch when waving hello&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brigitte&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Brigitte to reapply Repair Pack on her previous target rather than her new target if she used Repair Pack immediately after the cooldown ended&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Brigitte&#39;s Shield Bash hitbox to be wider than her shield&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Brigitte&#39;s Self-healing statistic being tracked&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doomfist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist&#39;s hand from animating when using Hand Cannon immediately after Rocket Punch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hanzo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Hanzo&#39;s Lunge animation to follow the direction of the first jump after changing directions on a subsequent jump&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Hanzo&#39;s hands to float above his legs during his Meditate emote with certain skins equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Hanzo&#39;s shins to appear malformed in his Heroic victory pose with his Scion skin equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from modifying Hanzo&#39;s Lunge ability cooldown in Custom Games&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevents Hanzo&#39;s reticle from constricting when using Storm Arrows&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lúcio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Lúcio&#39;s Soundwave animation to play twice if he used his quick melee attack immediately afterward&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;McCree&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the hammer on McCree&#39;s golden weapon variant to be dull with his Scrooge skin equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused McCree&#39;s ankles to deform when using his Take a Load Off emote&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mei&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes caused frozen targets to evade attacks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mei&#39;s Pajamei skin to exaggerate the curvature of her spine&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mei&#39;s Endothermic Blaster visual effects to go through shields&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mercy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mercy&#39;s wings to stretch out comically when waving hello while using Angelic Descent&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mercy to be placed too far towards the back of the victory hero line up&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Mercy&#39;s healing and damage boosting beams from being visible the first time it&#39;s used on a player after activating Valkyrie&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Orisa&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the pumpkin in Orisa&#39;s Pumpkin Head victory pose to persist after navigating away from it in the Hero Gallery&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reinhardt&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the player&#39;s camera to zoom into Reinhardt&#39;s Rocket Hammer when struck by it &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soldier: 76&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Soldier: 76&#39;s jacket collar to clip into his shoulder with his Classic skin equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sombra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Sombra&#39;s laser sight from tapering at its end with her Talon skin equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Symmetra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Symmetra&#39;s hard-light prism visual effects to deform into a sphere on the Hero Select screen&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Symmetra&#39;s Teleporter and Shield Generator to self-destruct when placed against certain walls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tracer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Tracer&#39;s Recall to appear jittery for spectators, in highlights, and in replays&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Torbjörn&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that made Torbjörn&#39;s turret lose sync with his breathing animation in his Medal victory pose&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Widowmaker&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a that caused Widowmaker&#39;s crosshair to disappear for a moment when scoping and unscoping&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winston&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Winston&#39;s shoulder to dislocate after using an emote&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Winston’s Jump Pack to stop short of its full distance when clearing ledges&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;May22_maps_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Maps&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;May22_maps_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Numbani&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused projectiles shot at Attacker spawn room doors to slide upward&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rialto&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the payload marker from appearing before the game started&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused players in the first Defender spawn room to make water splashing noises&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the payload thrusters from turning red when reversing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Genji&#39;s Cyber-agility and Hanzo&#39;s Wall Climb animations to loop and stutter when scaling walls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist to clip through the environment during his Combo highlight&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that allowed players to get a Play of the Game by killing gondoliers in Rialto&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watchpoint: Gibraltar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the heal icon from displaying on with the first Defender spawn room&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed defenders to see attacker spawn entrances&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-46836"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Patch 1.23.0.1</title>
    <updated>2018-05-08T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-05-08:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes caused the client to freeze&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-46510"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>