<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Overwatch PC Updates</title>
  <id>https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
  <updated>2018-01-23T12:01:21-08:00</updated>
  <subtitle>Patch notes and updates for Overwatch</subtitle>
  <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/"></link>
  <author>
    <name>Blizzard</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – January 23, 2018</title>
    <updated>2018-01-23T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-01-23:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Assault/Escort Map: Blizzard World&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Relive where you took your first steps in Azeroth, where you confronted the Lord of Terror, and where you spawned your first zerg rush—all of these epic memories come together on Overwatch’s newest Assault/Escort hybrid map, Blizzard World! This theme park brings the magic of Blizzard’s many worlds into one place so your most epic memories can come to life as you attack and defend the payload across Azeroth, Tristram, and the Koprulu Sector.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Blizzard World map will be disabled in Competitive Play until the start of Season 9. It will be available in Quick Play and Custom Games starting with today&#39;s patch. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cosmetics Update&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Starting now, loot boxes have been infused with over 100 cosmetics inspired by Blizzard World, Overwatch animated shorts, and more! Collect new legendary skins, including: Barbarian Zarya, Black Cat D.Va, Crusader Reinhardt, Ecopoint: Antarctica Mei, Kabuki Hanzo, and emotes such as Mercy’s Parasol, Sombra’s Marioneta, and Tracer’s Bomb Spin. Additionally, players will discover new highlight intros like Bastion’s Reconfigure, Soldier: 76’s Lights Out, Winston’s Roll, and many more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused weapon accuracy on the career profile to be displayed as 100%&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Junkrat’s Concussive Mine and Steel Trap to disappear if he placed them before using RIP-Tire&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-42936"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – January 9, 2018</title>
    <updated>2018-01-09T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-01-09:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overwatch League Skins Now Available&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Time to suit up, heroes! Starting now, you can directly support your favorite Overwatch League team (or teams!) by purchasing brand-new team skins to rep via the League Token system. Home-team skins are now available for all 12 teams and all 26 Heroes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Overwatch League team skins and the League Tokens, click &lt;a href=&#34;https://overwatchleague.com/en-us/news/21363697/team-skins-and-league-tokens-now-live&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;GENERAL UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Players can now watch the Overwatch League stream via the Overwatch League menu option when games are live&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Weapon accuracy is no longer increased or decreased when shooting at Genji’s Deflect or abilities that block projectiles (e.g. Winston’s Barrier Projector or Mei’s Ice Wall)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;User Interface Updates&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Zenyatta&#39;s Orb of Discord and Orb of Harmony will now display its target’s health bar&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented earned items from being displayed when a Loot Box was opened&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused a duplicate “Current Competitive Season” selection to appear in the Career Profile dropdown menu&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from being able to navigate in-game menus with the tab key&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented UI elements for Tracer’s Blink from displaying when switching between first- and third-person view in spectator mode&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the ammo count for Doomfist’s Hand Cannon from displaying when switching between first- and third-person view in spectator mode&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A.I.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the Bastion and Torbjörn bots from pathing to some areas on the first point of Eichenwalde&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the Lúcio bot to fall off the map while navigating King’s Row&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive Play&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the meters remaining to display twice when players approached the final five meters on Escort and Escort/Assault maps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Game Browser and Custom Games&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the Ultimate Duration Custom Game modification from properly adjusting Soldier: 76’s Ultimate length&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deathmatch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the Play of the Game highlight and the end-of-match screen to not display for the last player to die in the match&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Rocket Punch from destroying breakable objects&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that could cause Doomfist’s Rocket Punch knock back to be inconsistent if he collided with an enemy using a movement ability (e.g. Winston’s Leap)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a latency issue that caused Doomfist’s Rocket Punch to travel through an enemy instead of dealing damage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that sometimes caused Doomfist’s Rocket Punch’s directional movement to be unpredictable&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that allowed enemies to jump over Doomfist’s Rocket Punch instead of taking damage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused enemy players hit by Doomfist’s Rocket Punch to sometimes move along the wall impacted instead of taking damage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist to move along the terrain if he impacted it with Rocket Punch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused enemies hit by Doomfist’s Rocket Punch to impact inclines instead of traveling up them&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Rocket Punch to deal wall impact damage to Mercy if she used Valkyrie&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Rocket Punch to activate before intended if he was near Mei’s Ice Wall&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes caused Doomfist to fall through the ground if he used Seismic Slam on inclines&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that canceled Doomfist’s Seismic Slam when it was unable to reach the targeted location&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Junkrat’s RIP-Tire camera perspective to linger on the target after detonating&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Junkrat’s RIP-Tire to be silent to enemies while traveling on rooftops or when airborne&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes caused Snowball’s antenna to stretch out of proportion when Mei’s Beekeeper skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes caused Mercy’s Resurrect “Reviving” message to remain on the targeted player’s screen after the cast was finished&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused players targeted by Mercy’s Resurrect to no longer see their Respawn timer if her cast was interrupted by an enemy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from using Moira’s Biotic Orb if she used Fade or died while using Biotic Orb&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused Moira’s “Ultimate almost ready” voiceline to sometimes play when her Coalescence was fully charged&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Reinhardt’s Charge to knock back enemies instead of pinning them&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the visual effects of Sombra’s EMP to display when the ability was interrupted by an enemy player&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Sombra to face the incorrect direction after she teleported with Translocator&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes caused Torbjörn’s turrets to not fully heal when he used Molton Core&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Carbon Zenyatta’s in-game portrait from displaying the correct color&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug on Eichenwalde that caused the “Checkpoint Reached” voiceline to play when the payload reached its final destination&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Reaper to Shadow Step to unintended locations on Horizon Lunar Colony&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-42563"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – December 14, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-12-14T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2017-12-14:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused the game client to crash when certain visual effects were displayed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive Play&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug in Competitive Play that sometimes caused incorrect time adjustments between subsequent rounds on hybrid maps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes caused Roadhog’s Chain Hook to miss targets from certain angles and distances&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Torbjörn’s Forge Hammer from upgrading his turret when used at certain angles and distances&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-42210"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – December 12, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-12-12T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2017-12-12:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Seasonal Event: Winter Wonderland 2017&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;‘Tis the merriest time of year—Winter Wonderland is here!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From now until January 1, experience the holiday spirit with a brand-new brawl, Mei’s Yeti Hunt, and relive the previous Winter Wonderland’s magical moments by playing Mei’s Snowball Offensive. Players will also be able to unwrap loot boxes to collect last year’s festive fare in addition to 50 new holiday-themed cosmetics, including legendary skins like Snow Owl Ana, Avalanche Bastion, Beachrat Junkrat, Ice Fisherman Roadhog, Rime Sombra, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Winter Wonderland, click &lt;a href=&#34;https://playoverwatch.com/events/winter-wonderland/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Player Warning Updates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Several changes have been made to the player report system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Players being reported will receive an in-game message letting them know that they have been reported, along with a warning concerning continued negative behavior. Ongoing misconduct will result in silence, suspension, or a permanent ban, depending on the severity of the infraction (in severe cases, players may receive their punishment before receiving the initial in-game message).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Players who report someone for poor behavior, resulting in a disciplinary action, will now be notified with an in-game message when the issue has been resolved. We take every report seriously, along with your feedback. Thank you for your patience as we continue to fine tune these systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;GAME BROWSWER AND CUSTOM GAMES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added an option that allows heroes to spawn with fully charged ultimate abilities. This can be enabled under Settings &amp;gt; Heroes &amp;gt; General &amp;gt; Spawn with Ultimate Ready when creating a custom game&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added an option that allows heroes to cast ultimate abilities that last for the full duration of a match. This can be enabled under Settings &amp;gt; Heroes &amp;gt; General &amp;gt; Infinite Ultimate Duration when creating a custom game&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The length of time that hero ultimates remain active can now be adjusted. This slider can be found under Settings &amp;gt; Heroes &amp;gt; General &amp;gt; Ultimate Durations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A.I.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[PC] An option to “Remove All A.I.” in the custom game lobby can be accessed by Right Click &amp;gt; Remove All Bots&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[PS4] A.I. players can be removed from within the custom game lobby by selecting a bot, then selecting “Remove All Bots” from the submenu&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[XB1] A.I. players can be removed from within the custom game lobby by selecting a bot, then selecting “Remove All Bots” from the submenu&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;HERO GALLERY&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Players can now clear new item notifications with the “Mark All As Seen” button in the Hero Gallery&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused the arcade card for Limited Duel and Mystery Duel to not list all currently disabled characters&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[PC] Fixed an issue that prevented certain sound effects from playing when navigating the Options menu with a controller&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug in Elimination mode that caused players to spawn as a random hero at the start of a match instead of the one that was highlighted&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A.I.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Roadhog Bot to get stuck in the spawn room of the Oasis: City Center stage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a visual bug that caused Ana’s Biotic Rifle ammo clip to detach when her Captain Amari skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Rocket Punch from destroying objects&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Rocket Punch to not always deal damage when an enemy hits a wall&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Rocket Punch to not always stop an enemies&#39; movement when they impact a wall&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that canceled Doomfist’s Seismic Slam when it was unable to reach the targeted location&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused Doomfist’s Seismic Slam to trigger instantly when the ability was used to travel up inclines&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Seismic Slam to create performance drops when repeatedly used with no cooldown&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused D.Va’s Micro Missiles to not destroy breakable objects&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added green detail textures on Sparrow Genji&#39;s sword scabbard when the golden weapon variant is equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Hanzo’s Storm Bow reload from canceling if he used a melee attack after using his wall climbing ability&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Mei’s Cryo-freeze from clearing the healing debuff caused by Ana’s Biotic Grenade&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mercy’s Caduceus Blaster reload to be canceled if the player pressed the Resurrect keybind without a target to Resurrect&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that showed Mercy’s Guardian Angel targeting UI on allies while it was already in progress on a selected target&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed a Mercy player to cast Resurrect on a player that was in the process of being resurrected by another Mercy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Moira’s Biotic Orb to pass through terrain and structures&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented players from using Moira’s Biotic Orb’s regeneration option when primary fire was disabled&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a visual bug with Moira’s Biotic Orb that sometimes caused Biotic Grasp’s healing spray effects to display instead&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Moira’s Coalescence from healing an allied Reaper in Wraith Form&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Moira from being able to pass through enemies when using Fade&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Moira’s eyelashes to detach from her face during her Heroic highlight intro&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented Moira’s self-healing statistic from being collected and displayed in the game stats&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a visual issue with Moira’s Oasis skin that caused her knees to clip through her knee guards while crouched&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Reaper’s shotguns to animate incorrectly when discarded on the ground&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes allowed Reinhardt’s Charge to escape abilities that should prevent movement (e.g. Zarya’s Graviton Surge)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Widowmaker’s Grappling hook from pulling players to moveable objects, even when they were stationary (e.g. the window on the Eichenwalde Castle doors)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented highlights captured by Zenyatta players from recording correctly when the Cultist skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that allowed some heroes to hide on the Junkertown payload when using sit emotes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused a performance drop when players shot at the gold coin piles in the last Defender spawn of Junkertown&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-42076"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – November 30, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-11-30T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2017-11-30:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size:22px;&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moira&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Changed Moira’s ultimate ability name from Fusión to Coalescencia in Latin American Spanish (esMX)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added four new voice lines when Moira says her ultimate ability name in Latin American Spanish (esMX)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size:22px;&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COMPETITIVE PLAY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Made improvements to matchmaking that will decrease the range of Skill Rating between players on the same team&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;This change will help players get placed with allies and against opponents of a similar skill level, which should lead to more satisfying games.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size:22px;&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused the main menu to be unusable for certain players&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Moira’s Biotic Orb to pass through terrain and structures unintentionally&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-41773"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>