<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Overwatch PC Updates</title>
  <id>https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
  <updated>2017-12-14T22:05:18-08:00</updated>
  <subtitle>Patch notes and updates for Overwatch</subtitle>
  <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/"></link>
  <author>
    <name>Blizzard</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – December 14, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-12-14T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2017-12-14:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused the game client to crash when certain visual effects were displayed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive Play&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug in Competitive Play that sometimes caused incorrect time adjustments between subsequent rounds on hybrid maps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes caused Roadhog’s Chain Hook to miss targets from certain angles and distances&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Torbjörn’s Forge Hammer from upgrading his turret when used at certain angles and distances&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-42210"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – December 12, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-12-12T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2017-12-12:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Seasonal Event: Winter Wonderland 2017&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;‘Tis the merriest time of year—Winter Wonderland is here!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From now until January 1, experience the holiday spirit with a brand-new brawl, Mei’s Yeti Hunt, and relive the previous Winter Wonderland’s magical moments by playing Mei’s Snowball Offensive. Players will also be able to unwrap loot boxes to collect last year’s festive fare in addition to 50 new holiday-themed cosmetics, including legendary skins like Snow Owl Ana, Avalanche Bastion, Beachrat Junkrat, Ice Fisherman Roadhog, Rime Sombra, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Winter Wonderland, click &lt;a href=&#34;https://playoverwatch.com/events/winter-wonderland/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Player Warning Updates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Several changes have been made to the player report system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Players being reported will receive an in-game message letting them know that they have been reported, along with a warning concerning continued negative behavior. Ongoing misconduct will result in silence, suspension, or a permanent ban, depending on the severity of the infraction (in severe cases, players may receive their punishment before receiving the initial in-game message).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Players who report someone for poor behavior, resulting in a disciplinary action, will now be notified with an in-game message when the issue has been resolved. We take every report seriously, along with your feedback. Thank you for your patience as we continue to fine tune these systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;GAME BROWSWER AND CUSTOM GAMES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added an option that allows heroes to spawn with fully charged ultimate abilities. This can be enabled under Settings &amp;gt; Heroes &amp;gt; General &amp;gt; Spawn with Ultimate Ready when creating a custom game&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added an option that allows heroes to cast ultimate abilities that last for the full duration of a match. This can be enabled under Settings &amp;gt; Heroes &amp;gt; General &amp;gt; Infinite Ultimate Duration when creating a custom game&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The length of time that hero ultimates remain active can now be adjusted. This slider can be found under Settings &amp;gt; Heroes &amp;gt; General &amp;gt; Ultimate Durations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A.I.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[PC] An option to “Remove All A.I.” in the custom game lobby can be accessed by Right Click &amp;gt; Remove All Bots&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[PS4] A.I. players can be removed from within the custom game lobby by selecting a bot, then selecting “Remove All Bots” from the submenu&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[XB1] A.I. players can be removed from within the custom game lobby by selecting a bot, then selecting “Remove All Bots” from the submenu&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;HERO GALLERY&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Players can now clear new item notifications with the “Mark All As Seen” button in the Hero Gallery&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused the arcade card for Limited Duel and Mystery Duel to not list all currently disabled characters&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[PC] Fixed an issue that prevented certain sound effects from playing when navigating the Options menu with a controller&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug in Elimination mode that caused players to spawn as a random hero at the start of a match instead of the one that was highlighted&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A.I.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Roadhog Bot to get stuck in the spawn room of the Oasis: City Center stage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a visual bug that caused Ana’s Biotic Rifle ammo clip to detach when her Captain Amari skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Rocket Punch from destroying objects&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Rocket Punch to not always deal damage when an enemy hits a wall&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Rocket Punch to not always stop an enemies&#39; movement when they impact a wall&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that canceled Doomfist’s Seismic Slam when it was unable to reach the targeted location&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused Doomfist’s Seismic Slam to trigger instantly when the ability was used to travel up inclines&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Seismic Slam to create performance drops when repeatedly used with no cooldown&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused D.Va’s Micro Missiles to not destroy breakable objects&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added green detail textures on Sparrow Genji&#39;s sword scabbard when the golden weapon variant is equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Hanzo’s Storm Bow reload from canceling if he used a melee attack after using his wall climbing ability&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Mei’s Cryo-freeze from clearing the healing debuff caused by Ana’s Biotic Grenade&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mercy’s Caduceus Blaster reload to be canceled if the player pressed the Resurrect keybind without a target to Resurrect&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that showed Mercy’s Guardian Angel targeting UI on allies while it was already in progress on a selected target&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed a Mercy player to cast Resurrect on a player that was in the process of being resurrected by another Mercy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Moira’s Biotic Orb to pass through terrain and structures&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented players from using Moira’s Biotic Orb’s regeneration option when primary fire was disabled&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a visual bug with Moira’s Biotic Orb that sometimes caused Biotic Grasp’s healing spray effects to display instead&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Moira’s Coalescence from healing an allied Reaper in Wraith Form&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Moira from being able to pass through enemies when using Fade&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Moira’s eyelashes to detach from her face during her Heroic highlight intro&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented Moira’s self-healing statistic from being collected and displayed in the game stats&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a visual issue with Moira’s Oasis skin that caused her knees to clip through her knee guards while crouched&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Reaper’s shotguns to animate incorrectly when discarded on the ground&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes allowed Reinhardt’s Charge to escape abilities that should prevent movement (e.g. Zarya’s Graviton Surge)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Widowmaker’s Grappling hook from pulling players to moveable objects, even when they were stationary (e.g. the window on the Eichenwalde Castle doors)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented highlights captured by Zenyatta players from recording correctly when the Cultist skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that allowed some heroes to hide on the Junkertown payload when using sit emotes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused a performance drop when players shot at the gold coin piles in the last Defender spawn of Junkertown&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-42076"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – November 30, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-11-30T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2017-11-30:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size:22px;&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moira&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Changed Moira’s ultimate ability name from Fusión to Coalescencia in Latin American Spanish (esMX)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added four new voice lines when Moira says her ultimate ability name in Latin American Spanish (esMX)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size:22px;&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COMPETITIVE PLAY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Made improvements to matchmaking that will decrease the range of Skill Rating between players on the same team&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;This change will help players get placed with allies and against opponents of a similar skill level, which should lead to more satisfying games.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size:22px;&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused the main menu to be unusable for certain players&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Moira’s Biotic Orb to pass through terrain and structures unintentionally&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-41773"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – November 16, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-11-16T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2017-11-16:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Hero: Moira (Support):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wielding both regenerative and degenerative technologies at her fingertips, &lt;strong&gt;Moira&lt;/strong&gt; O’Deorain is Talon’s ambitious geneticist who seeks the knowledge to rewrite the building blocks of human life by any means necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moira’s cutting-edge capabilities make her a mobile healer and damage dealer capable of adapting to any situation. Her main attack is &lt;strong&gt;Biotic Grasp&lt;/strong&gt;, which she can use to either heal allies or sap an enemy’s life force. Biotic Grasp’s primary fire sprays a cone of energy that heals all teammates within range, draining biotic energy while active, which will replenish slowly over time. Her alternate fire is a beam that tethers to enemies, dealing damage and siphoning health. Draining her foes’ health regenerates Moira’s biotic energy even faster, allowing more healing for her allies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Her &lt;strong&gt;Biotic Orb&lt;/strong&gt; ability launches a sphere of energy that bounces around the battlefield, healing nearby allies or damaging enemies until it dissipates. &lt;strong&gt;Fade&lt;/strong&gt; enables Moira to disappear out of sight and sprint through the shadows, and makes her invulnerable for its duration. When Moira’s ultimate is ready to be unleashed, she can cast &lt;strong&gt;Coalescence&lt;/strong&gt;—a powerful, long-range beam of chaotic energy that pierces through barriers to heal allies or damage enemies in its path.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;centered&#34; style=&#34;margin-bottom:25px;&#34;&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/8tLopqeL9s8?theme=light&amp;amp;color=white&amp;amp;cc_load_policy=1&amp;amp;HD=1&amp;amp;rel=0&amp;amp;showinfo=0&#34; style=&#34;border-bottom:1px solid lightgray;&#34; width=&#34;560&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Moira, click &lt;a href=&#34;https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/heroes/moira/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;As with all new heroes, please note that Moira’s release in Competitive Play will be delayed by one week.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;GENERAL UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Clicking the &#34;leave game as group&#34; checkbox will now remember your selection for future matches&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Arcade&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;One of the arcade slots will now change on a daily basis to include a variety of game modes such as Limited Duel, Low Gravity, and Capture the Flag&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ana&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Biotic Rifle&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Damage increased from 60 to 70&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ana has been outshined by other support heroes lately. Boosting her damage will help her defend herself and make her more threatening to the enemy team.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lúcio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lúcio now has an effect above his head to indicate which song he&#39;s playing in spectator mode&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mercy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Caduceus Staff&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Increased visual readability of Mercy&#39;s healing and damage boosting beams&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Resurrect&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cast time increased from 0 seconds to 1.75 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mercy&#39;s movement speed is now reduced by 75% while casting&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Can now be interrupted when Mercy is knocked back, stunned, or hacked&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Valkyrie&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;While active, Resurrect no longer has a cast time&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;While active, casting Resurrect does not reduce Mercy&#39;s movement speed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comment: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;We feel that Mercy’s recent rework has been successful, but her Resurrect ability still feels too strong and frustrating to play against. Now that it has a cast time, enemies are more able to counter the ability. However, Resurrect will cast instantly when Valkyrie is active. This should make her feel powerful when she transforms on the battlefield.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winston&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Barrier Projector&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now displays a health bar&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comment: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;This change will help both Winston&#39;s allies and enemies know how much more damage his shield can absorb from oncoming attacks.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;COMPETITIVE PLAY&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Grandmaster players can now only group up with other players within 250 Skill Rating&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comment: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;We have tightened the Skill Rating range that Grandmaster players can group up with from 500 SR down to 250 SR. This is to ensure our highest ranked players are playing with equally skilled people, which should lead to more satisfying games.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;USER INTERFACE&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Made several visual adjustments to revamp the spectator mode HUD including an improved spectator mode UI, a new unit frame style, and an animated ultimate indicator&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented player portrait borders from loading in the Hero Select screen or on the Match Status screen&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from adding spectators to a Deathmatch game from within the Custom Game lobby&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A.I.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented bots from respawning when they were moved to a different slot or team within the Custom Game lobby&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the Sombra bot from hacking health packs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that affected the Bastion bot’s movement when defending Point A on Eichenwalde&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented bots from defending Point A on certain maps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Ana’s sidearm to emit a bright light when viewed in the Hero Gallery&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented Ganymede from making appropriate roadrunner noises when Bastion’s Dune Buggy skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Mercy’s ultimate icon from displaying correctly when hacked by Sombra&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue causing Roadhog’s Chain Hook to latch on to enemy players for longer than intended&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an animation bug that caused Widowmaker’s knees to snap together when jumping&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused the toy robot in Zarya’s Mystery Gift emote to inflate when she tore it apart&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented Junkrat’s RIP-Tire from casting properly while jumping&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the incorrect stage of the map (e.g. Sanctum on Nepal) to be displayed during the hero selection phase when playing on Nepal and Lijiang Tower&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the progress bar from displaying briefly when players reached checkpoints on Escort and Escort/Assault maps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented the targeting UI on Doomfist’s Seismic Slam from functioning correctly when aiming at the spinning turbine blade near the last point of Junkertown&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused some objects to uncharacteristically fly across the room when shot on Horizon Lunar Colony&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-41350"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – October 17, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-10-17T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2017-10-17:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;GENERAL UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Players can now set their social status to Online, Away, Busy, or Appear Offline (Note: appearing offline does not prevent friends from seeing you if you are placed into the same match). This option can be found under the social menu&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lúcio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Wall Ride&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The speed boost that Lúcio receives after completing a wall ride has been increased by 65%&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;A recent bug fix slowed Lúcio’s Wall Ride. This change compensates for the reduced speed.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mercy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Guardian Angel&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Players can now glide past a targeted ally using the jump key&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cooldown no longer resets when Resurrect is activated&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Valkyrie&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No longer resets or reduces Resurrection’s cooldown&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now gives players a bonus resurrection charge&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comment: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Valkyrie no longer resets or reduces Resurrect’s cooldown. Instead, it now provides an extra &#39;charge,&#39; allowing you to revive an ally even if it is still on cooldown. If the bonus charge hasn’t been spent when Valkyrie ends, it will be removed.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This method makes Resurrect more flexible when used with Valkyrie. For example, in the past if you wanted to resurrect two teammates, you had to revive the first target, then activate Valkyrie (causing the Resurrect’s cooldown to reset), and then revive the other target. With this change, you can now activate Valkyrie and fly in quickly to resurrect both targets instantly.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;However, this still reduces the overall number of Resurrects that Mercy can provide, since Valkyrie no longer reduces its cooldown.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zenyatta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added a number of additional voicelines for Cultist Zenyatta&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug preventing Mercy’s momentum from slowing down correctly when Guardian Angel was canceled&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug preventing the visual effects on Sombra’s Pumpkinette victory pose from displaying correctly&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-40570"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>