<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Overwatch PC Updates</title>
  <id>https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
  <updated>2018-03-29T12:01:14-07:00</updated>
  <subtitle>Patch notes and updates for Overwatch</subtitle>
  <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/"></link>
  <author>
    <name>Blizzard</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch PTR Patch Notes – March 29, 2018</title>
    <updated>2018-03-29T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-03-29:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;GAMEPLAY UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Turrets no longer target barriers directly, but will still target enemies behind them&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused visual effects to be absorbed into surfaces&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;&#x9; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused turrets to target Brigitte’s Barrier Shield while facing them when the shield wasn’t deployed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Reaper to reach unintended locations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-45214"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – March 20, 2018</title>
    <updated>2018-03-20T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-03-20:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Hero: Brigitte (Support):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An engineer with peerless armor-constructing abilities, &lt;strong&gt;Brigitte&lt;/strong&gt; Lindholm is a valiant squire who fights on the front line to protect her allies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Brigitte’s armor engineering capabilities make her a stalwart support hero, capable of holding her ground in combat while also providing healing and armor for her teammates. Her primary weapon is her heavy-hitting &lt;b&gt;Rocket Flail&lt;/b&gt; that she swings in a wide arc in front of her to smash multiple enemies at once. &lt;b&gt;Whip Shot&lt;/b&gt; enables Brigitte to fling her flail forward, striking enemies at a distance and knocking them backward. With each blow, Brigitte’s passive ability, &lt;b&gt;Inspire&lt;/b&gt;, heals nearby allies over time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Brigitte’s &lt;b&gt;Barrier Shield&lt;/b&gt; deploys a frontal energy barrier that can absorb a limited amount of damage and protect any allies directly behind her. Once her Barrier Shield is deployed, she can use &lt;b&gt;Shield Bash&lt;/b&gt; to lunge forward and stun the first enemy in her path. Drawing on her engineering prowess, Brigitte can create &lt;b&gt;Repair Packs&lt;/b&gt; to instantly heal wounded allies or provide armor to teammates at maximum health. When Brigitte is at her strongest, she can activate her ultimate ability, &lt;b&gt;Rally&lt;/b&gt;—a galvanizing call to arms that generates a substantial amount of armor for nearby allies and increases Brigitte’s movement speed so she can lead them into battle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Brigitte, click &lt;a href=&#34;&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Brigitte will be available in Competitive Play in Season 10. To learn more, click &lt;a href=&#34;&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;GENERAL UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Changed the name of Junkrat’s Scarecrow spray to Hayseed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Updated Mercy’s Toast victory pose&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sombra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hack&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now goes on a 2-second cooldown when interrupted by damage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now more consistently interrupted when targets break line of sight&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; Developer Comments: We’re also removing the 0.1 second window of time during a hack where it couldn’t be canceled via line of sight or with other abilities including Tracer’s Recall and Zarya’s Particle Barrier, which was originally put in place so the hack wouldn’t be interrupted by small objects such as light posts. We’ve implemented a separate fix for that issue, so she should still be unaffected by those small objects.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;USER INTERFACE UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Team Information Screen now displays the ultimate charge of your teammates&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Rocket Punch from traveling forward if he had been hit by an enemy Doomfist’s Rising Uppercut&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes prevented players from aiming Doomfist’s Rocket Punch when facing an enemy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that allowed players to jump over Doomfist’s Rocket Punch when on an incline&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Seismic Slam to cancel if he could not get close to his target&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Rising Uppercut cooldown countdown from displaying if he was in a movement hindering ability (e.g. Zarya’s Graviton Surge or Junkrat’s Steel Trap)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Rocket Punch cooldown to delay counting down if he was in a movement hindering ability (e.g. Zarya’s Graviton Surge or Junkrat’s Steel Trap)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Rocket Punch from hitting enemies that were close to him&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Junkrat’s RIP-Tire kills from being credited in the Kill Feed if the targets had a long death animation (e.g. D.Va’s Mech)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mercy’s Regeneration to occur instantly if she took damage while at full health&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mercy’s wings to separate from her body if her Zhuque skin was equipped during her Toast victory pose&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Moira’s Biotic Orb from receiving kill credit if it expired at the same time it killed an enemy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Moira’s Fade visual effects to indicate the direction she was traveling in when she used the ability&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Reinhardt’s Charge from pinning enemies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the chunks from the pumpkin in Reinhardt’s Pumpkin Smash emote from appearing after he obliterated it with his Rocket Hammer&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Roadhog’s Chain Hook to appear at the top of an opponent’s screen if he used it against an enemy Mercy when she used Valkyrie&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Sombra from receiving environmental kill credit if she kills an enemy using Hack&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes caused Sombra to be visible to enemies without displaying a “Detected” notification during Stealth&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes failed to teleport players using Symmetra’s Teleporter if they used an ability that increased their movement speed when passing through it (e.g. Doomfist’s Rocket Punch)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused some objects to block projectiles on Blizzard World (e.g. souvenir carts)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the “Restore Defaults” button from resetting all settings in the Social Options tab&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused players to delete characters in the “Save Highlight” text box if they pressed down the delete input while their settings were below 60 FPS&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the user interface to indicate two control points on a single control point map when playing a custom game&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-44916"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – February 27, 2018</title>
    <updated>2018-02-27T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-02-27:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doomfist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hand Cannon&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ammo recovery rate increased from 0.8 seconds to 0.65 seconds per bullet&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; This change will help Doomfist more consistently be able to use his weapon as part of his combos.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mei&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Endothermic Blaster&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Freeze (slow) duration increased from 1 second to 1.5 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Weapon alternate fire ammo cost reduced from 25 to 20&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comment: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Increasing Mei’s slow duration helps her freeze targets that are particularly elusive such as Genji or Lúcio. Lowering her alternate fire ammo cost allows her to more safely use it without costing her the ability to freeze enemies.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sombra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;EMP&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No longer blocked by small objects (e.g. sign posts)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hack&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No longer gains ultimate charge from health pack healing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cast time reduced from 0.8 seconds to 0.65 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now disables the following abilities:&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Genji—Cyber-agility&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hanzo—Wall Climb&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Pharah—Hover Jets&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lúcio—Healing Boost and Speed Boost (turns off current song entirely), Wall Ride&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mercy—Angelic Descent&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Machine Pistol&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Machine Pistol spread reduced from 3 to 2.7&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Opportunist&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enemy health bars are now visible when health drops below 100% (formerly 50%)&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Her ability to detect enemies through walls at 50% or less remains unchanged&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Translocator&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Duration increased from 15 seconds to 20 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comment: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The goal of these changes for Sombra is to remove the necessity for her teammates to take damage and heal themselves with her hacked heath packs to try to get her ultimate charged up quickly. Her ultimate will now come up less often, but there are more abilities that are disabled by Hack so it is more effective when used. Previously, Opportunist would only activate when an enemy’s health bar dipped below 50% but now the passive will reveal all damaged enemies which should help Sombra identify targets in her line of sight to pick off. Overall these changes should make her more effective and less reliant on her ultimate.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;MAP UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blizzard World&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Some health pack sizes have been reduced&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Some health pack locations have been changed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Additional health packs have been added&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; Health packs are a valuable resource in Overwatch and positioning around them is key to holding ground on defense or keeping up momentum on offense. We have moved the location of some health packs and included additional ones to improve game play on Blizzard World.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;USER INTERFACE UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mercy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Valkyrie&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No longer shows enemies’ health bars unless they have taken damage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comment: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;This helps remove some clutter from Mercy players’ screens when they use her ultimate&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Capture the Flag statistics from displaying on the Career Profile if the match was played on Ayuttheya in the Arcade&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes prevented announcement voice lines from triggering on Blizzard World&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-44022"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – February 13, 2018</title>
    <updated>2018-02-13T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-02-13:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lúcio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Wall Ride&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Activating Wall Ride will now cause the flag to drop during Capture the Flag matches&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;stron&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lúcio’s Wall Ride allowed him to reach unintended places in Capture the Flag maps, which made it overly difficult for opponents to stop him. So, we have changed the ability to cause the flag to drop instead for better balanced matches.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/stron&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a typo that caused the Lunar New Year banner to display the wrong end date for Overwatch Lunar New Year&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes caused the client to crash after a player used the Hero Skin Selection dropdown menu in Hero Select&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capture the Flag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Winston to pick up the flag while airborne after activating his Jump Pack&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused flags dropped near ceilings to get stuck inside of walls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deathmatch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mei to levitate if she used Cryo-stasis&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Game Browser and Custom Games&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from playing games in the Arcade if they were using a trial account&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused hero ultimate charges to reset after the first death if a player changed their skin using the Hero Skin Selection a second before the match began&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Zarya’s reaction animations to loop continuously after taking damage following the destruction of her Particle Barrier&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the Weekly Rewards timer in from displaying correctly in the Arcade&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-43605"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – February 8, 2018</title>
    <updated>2018-02-08T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-02-08:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Seasonal Event: Lunar New Year 2018&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Get ready to ring in the Year of the Dog!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year, we’re celebrating Lunar New Year with over 50 new seasonal items including legendary skins like Red Phoenix (Zhu Que) Mercy, Black Tortoise (Xuan Wu) Zarya, White Tiger (Bai Hu) Genji, and Black Lily Widowmaker. Experience our updates to our Capture the Flag mode—including a competitive Capture the Flag mode and Sudden Death—on a brand-new map, Ayutthaya.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about the new Capture the Flag changes, click &lt;a href=&#34;https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20761736983#1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hero Skin Selection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fashion-forward heroes, rejoice! Players can now change hero skins with the “Select Skin” dropdown menu in the Hero Select screen at the start of a match. Show off your favorite unlocked skins when playing solo or coordinate with your friends to be the best dressed on the battlegrounds of tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doomfist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hand Cannon&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Damage reduced from 11 to 6&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Number of bullets fired increased from 6 to 11&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Spread pattern made more consistent&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;We have made a lot of progress with Doomfist’s movement in recent patches but we wanted to revisit his Hand Cannon. While the damage per bullet has been lowered, the number of bullets he fires per Hand Cannon shot has been increased which makes his overall damage output unchanged. Overall, these changes will help his Hand Cannon feel much more consistent.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;USER INTERFACE UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Matchmaking UI now displays the game mode players have queued for while waiting for players&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Competitive Play leaver messages now display as a chat notification&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Hero Select screen now displays the game mode and map type&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Zenyatta’s Orb of Discord and Orb of Harmony will now display its target’s hero name&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the mouse cursor to lose focus when using third party overlays (e.g. Discord)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that sometimes prevented the Overwatch League scheduled matches of the day from loading&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented bots from voting on cards at the end of the match on Hybrid and Control maps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive Play&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented capture progress UI on Assault and Hybrid maps from displaying the correct team colors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed players to use the Hero Select screen during the loading screen at the start of a match&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deathmatch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Widowmaker’s Infra-sight from functioning if it was used at the same time as another Widowmaker’s Infra-sight&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Torbjörn to collide with his turret&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Symmetra’s Sentry Turrets to continue targeting Junkrat’s Steel Trap after it was destroyed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from being able to stand on top of enemy players&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed backfilling players to enter at 9th place during the match&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused targets hacked by Sombra to appear purple instead of red&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the displayed hero on the lobby screen to appear in low detail when entering and exiting the Overwatch League screen&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Game Browser and Custom Games&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed players to summon infinite bots in custom games&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused D.Va to lose her Self-Destruct ultimate if she died out of her mech when the “Spawn with Ultimate Ready” option was enabled&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the Victory voice line to play when a match ended in a draw while spectating&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused airborne heroes to lose speed when changing direction&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented golden weapon visual effects from displaying when an Overwatch League skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused heroes’ scoped shots to be calculated as misses in the accuracy statistic&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Ana’s Candy emote from displaying when viewing Kill Cam footage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Rocket Punch to impact with D.Va’s mech before it materialized during her Call Mech ability&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented kills caused by Doomfist’s Rocket Punch from receiving environmental kill credit&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Genji from sheathing his katana after using his Whirlwind emote&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Genji from using his Cyber-agility occasionally&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Hanzo’s Dragonstrike to be calculated in the accuracy statistic&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Hanzo’s Wall Climb from activating occasionally&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mercy’s Caduceus Staff to disappear when using the Parasol emote&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mercy to fly in an unintended direction if she was stunned during Guardian Angel&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Mercy from destroying breakables she collides with in her flight path when using Guardian Angel&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mercy’s Valkyrie flight controls to not be precise when using Resurrect&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Moira’s Biotic Grasp’s hits against barriers to be calculated as misses in her accuracy statistic&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that extended the cooldown of Orisa’s Halt! by one second if it successfully pulled an enemy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Sombra to block Reaper’s Death Blossom if she used her Marioneta emote&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Reinhardt to have a blank expression during his Toast victory pose&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed projectiles to sometimes penetrate Reinhardt’s Barrier Field&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Reinhardt’s Charge bonus damage from being dealt if the target was sandwiched between a charging friendly Reinhardt and a charging enemy Reinhardt&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Reinhardt to knock back a target instead of pinning them if he collided with an enemy at the start of his Charge&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Roadhog’s canister from appearing when viewing Overwatch League skins&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Roadhog’s Chain Hook to clip the first-person camera when pulling in a target&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Sombra’s EMP from canceling an enemy Sombra’s Hack if it was in progress&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s Shield Generator from displaying in the Overwatch League skin preview screen&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Torbjörn’s lava ball from appearing in his Batter Up emote if his hammer was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Widowmaker’s hair to not hang properly in the Hanging Around Highlight Intro when an Overwatch League skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Widowmaker’s Venom Mine to use Overwatch League team colors when an Overwatch League skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Widowmaker’s Grappling Hook animation from playing when using the ability&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Winston to lose some upward momentum when using Jump Pack off small inclines&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Overwatch League team decals to disappear from Winston’s suit when he used Primal Rage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Zenyatta’s Discord Orb to fly in an odd direction if its target died before arriving&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hero Gallery&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from purchasing non-hero sprays&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused some heroes to get stuck behind the lamp post directly outside the first Defender spawn room in Blizzard World&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that allowed players to reach unintended locations in Blizzard World&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented D.Va’s Micro Missiles from passing through piñatas on Dorado&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Junkrat’s RIP-tire to travel under the trailer at the final point on Hollywood&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Moira’s Biotic Orbs from bouncing off the wooden pillars on Hollywood&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the UI to show a fraction of a meter to go when reaching checkpoints on Escort and Assault/Escort maps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the hero portrait from displaying when watching Highlights when an Overwatch League skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented player portraits from displaying during the Play of the Game, Kill Cam, Spectating, and Highlights&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-43435"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>