<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Overwatch PC Updates</title>
  <id>https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
  <updated>2018-09-11T12:00:50-07:00</updated>
  <subtitle>Patch notes and updates for Overwatch</subtitle>
  <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/"></link>
  <author>
    <name>Blizzard</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Patch 1.28.0.1</title>
    <updated>2018-09-11T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-09-11:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeadingBanner&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/fo/FOM4P1Q9LS561536622019781.jpg);&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;HeadingBanner-header&#34;&gt;SEPTEMBER 11, 2018&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pick your heroes and pack your bags—we’re traveling to Busan!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In our newest map, heroes will fight in the heart of South Korea, home to former professional gamer and famed MEKA pilot, D.Va. Over the past six months, I’ve worked on creating the environment and buildings within each of Busan’s three stages: Sanctuary, Downtown, and MEKA Base.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We released this map alongside our latest cinematic short featuring D.Va, Shooting Star. Because of this, we worked closely with the cinematics department to recreate the MEKA Base as closely as possible. We wanted players to feel like they’re in the film as soon as they load into the map. This is the first time we’ve done this kind of collaboration, and we think it was a success! The way the map looks in game and in the short are much more similar than our previous attempts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That said, it’s not a straight one-to-one. In the game, in addition to looking great, a map needs to be playable and—most importantly—fun. As such, we expanded and built out parts of the MEKA Base that made it intuitive for players to understand the space they’re in and to offer unique gameplay moments. You can see one of these changes on the control point in the MEKA Base. There are three blast shields that go up and down, providing cover from enemy fire. An alarm accompanied by a flashing light and steam indicates when the shields will rise from the ground, signaling to the team that it is safe to attack the point. This is the first time we’ve intentionally designed moving terrain as part of a map’s strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The whole team poured a lot of love and effort into capturing the likeness of Busan and building out the story of D.Va and South Korea. You may notice that D.Va’s room inside the MEKA Base is full of trophies she won as a professional gamer, along with a top-of-the-line gaming rig—and even a couple of cans of Nano Cola.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We really do hope that you will love playing on this map, and we’re looking forward to reading and hearing what you have to say about it!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;—Simon Fuchs, Senior Environment Artist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;NEW MAP – BUSAN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/r4/R4F6V9FND6HG1536622033915.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Travel to &lt;strong&gt;Busan&lt;/strong&gt;, South Korea and battle for control across three distinct locales within one map: &lt;strong&gt;Sanctuary&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Downtown&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;MEKA Base&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Explore the serene setting of the &lt;strong&gt;Sanctuary&lt;/strong&gt;, surrounded by an ancient temple, beautiful gardens, and historic architecture. Clash in the bustling metropolis of &lt;strong&gt;Downtown&lt;/strong&gt;, where players will fight across a busy PC bang, flashy karaoke bar, and central light rail station (just watch out for the train). Contest for position in &lt;strong&gt;MEKA Base&lt;/strong&gt;—home of South Korea’s frontline defense against the gwishin omnic attacks: D.Va and the rest of the MEKA squad.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;HERO GALLERY – FILTER&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/tp/TPMX6UMVV9EI1536622048047.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;View all of the cosmetics Overwatch has to offer with our new Filter feature in the Hero Gallery. Customize your search for cosmetics by category (including seasonal events or whether they&#39;re from the Overwatch League), rarity, and whether they are unlocked or waiting to be collected.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;GENERAL UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added visual outlines to make allies visible through walls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; While this is a bug fix, we wanted to highlight this change as it can affect gameplay by changing the damage output of the affected heroes in certain situations. After this fix, weapons with spread should now correctly calculate critical damage for each individual pellet that lands in a critical region (e.g. a headshot). The end result of this change is that it should be significantly easier to deal critical damage with any weapon that fires multiple shots simultaneously, such as Reaper’s Hellfire Shotguns and D.Va’s Fusion Cannons. In addition, we’ve changed the logic for when these weapons display a critical marker on your screen. It now requires 30% of your shots to be critical, rather than displaying it if a single pellet hits critically.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that would cause some weapons that fired multiple shots at once to inconsistently deal critical damage (e.g. Doomfist’s Hand Cannon, D.Va’s Fusion Cannons, Genji’s Shurikens, Reaper’s Hellfire Shotguns, Torbjörn’s Rivet Gun)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Ana&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/xl/XL6RBC3KRLAQ1527630418946.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Biotic Rifle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Increased the precision of the Relative Aim Sensitivity While Zoomed slider. This can be found under Options &amp;gt; Controls &amp;gt; Hero &amp;gt; Ana&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Brigitte&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/bw/BWLZGE8PVBJI1527630462150.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; Currently, when two charging targets hit each other, they both fall down and are briefly stunned. You can see this interaction with Doomfist’s Rocket Punch and Reinhardt’s Charge abilities. Brigitte’s Shield Bash previously wasn’t included in this group, which meant that if she used Shield Bash against these other abilities, she would generally stun them and not be affected herself. This change makes it so if she uses Shield Bash against Charge or Rocket Punch, both players will be knocked down.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;brigitte&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Shield Bash&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now knocks down and gets knocked down by other charging targets (e.g Reinhardt and Doomfist)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Reinhardt&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/oh/OHE7FR3IMSFZ1533749721401.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; We’ve given Earthshatter a complete overhaul to combat inconsistencies with its performance. These changes will make Earthshatter’s behavior more predictable and effective.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;doomfist&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Earthshatter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now consistently hits enemies near walls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No longer hits enemies that enter the damage cone after the “wave” has passed that area&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No longer damages enemies behind barriers blocking it, even if the barrier is later dropped or destroyed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Always travels up inclines and around the payload&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Widowmaker&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/y5/Y53MJB70RQYS1533749821829.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Grappling Hook&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now retains momentum when used on environments or structures without a ledge (e.g. walls)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Widow&#39;s Kiss&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Increased the precision of the Relative Aim Sensitivity While Zoomed slider. This can be found under Options &amp;gt; Controls &amp;gt; Hero &amp;gt; Widowmaker&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;COMPETITIVE PLAY UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Grand Master players can now group with players within 350 Skill Rating, up from 250 Skill Rating&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;GAME BROWSER AND CUSTOM GAMES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Modified the Respawn Time Scalar custom game option to prevent respawn times longer than the default&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FFA Deathmatch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mercy now begins the match with her Caduceus Blaster equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Blizzard World is now available to play in Deathmatch and Team Deathmatch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1v1 Mystery Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mercy now begins the match with her Caduceus Blaster equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;MAP UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Rialto&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Payload travel speed has been slightly increased&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Amount of time the payload pauses at checkpoints has been reduced&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;September11_General_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;September11_General_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused players to sometimes slip off railings&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Torbjörn Armor Packs Created statistic from updating if the ability landed directly on a friendly target&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;September11_CommunicationWheel_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Communication Wheel&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;September11_CommunicationWheel_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused a delay in selecting options on the Communication Wheel when cycling left using a mouse&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;September11_heroes_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Heroes&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;September11_heroes_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brigitte&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Brigitte’s Shield Bash movement to be interrupted when she impacted Symmetra’s turrets&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doomfist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Seismic Slam to cancel when using Symmetra’s Teleporter&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;D.Va&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed D.Va to escape the map if she used Call Mech while standing on Mei’s Ice Wall&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hanzo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the Dragonstrike arrow&#39;s size to be larger than his other arrows&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mei&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mei’s Cryo-freeze to block the line of sight for Mei’s Blizzard&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mercy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Mercy to gain ultimate charge from using her damage beam on attacks that cannot be damage boosted&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reaper&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Reaper’s Shadow Step from going on cooldown if he was interrupted&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reinhardt&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Reinhardt to pin targets that were behind him when using Charge&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Reinhardt from pinning some targets when he turned during Charge&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Reinhardt to use Earthshatter while standing on an enemy’s head&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes prevented Reinhardt’s Earthshatter from hitting enemies standing on a payload&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Reinhardt’s Earthshatter from traveling up certain inclines&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Roadhog&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes caused Roadhog’s Chain Hook to break after hitting an enemy while maintaining line of sight&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Roadhog’s alternate fire from calculating falloff damage correctly&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes prevented Reinhardt’s Earthshatter from landing if he was launched into the air while activating it&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sombra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Sombra from translocating to a moving platform&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Sombra from destroying her Translocator if she was stunned or hacked&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Sombra’s Translocator from accurately indicating where Sombra would arrive when the ability was used&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Symmetra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Sombra’s Hack from canceling Symmetra’s Photon Barrier placement&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Symmetra’s teleport UI to persist after being eliminated&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Widowmaker&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Widowmaker’s Grappling Hook from connecting to some ledges&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Widowmaker’s scoped shots on hero placed objects to count against her Scoped Weapon Accuracy statistic (e.g. Symmetra’s Teleporter, Torbjörn’s autocannon)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wrecking Ball&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Wrecking Ball’s Piledriver from dealing falloff damage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Wrecking Ball’s Piledriver to deal damage twice if he slid off the environment during its duration&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Wrecking Ball’s primary fire to continue working even if it was disabled in custom game&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-50483"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Patch 1.27.1.1</title>
    <updated>2018-08-28T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-08-28:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class=&#34;HeadingBanner&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/jf/JF06XUJAJQPL1535416065570.jpg);&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;HeadingBanner-header&#34;&gt;AUGUST 28, 2018&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;D.Va’s Nano Cola Challenge&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/aj/AJI4DD9K5CIU1535416124606.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re celebrating the release of D.Va’s action-packed animated “Shooting Star” short by making some special content available to unlock in-game. For a limited time, your wins in Quick Play, Competitive Play, or Arcade will all earn you additional D.Va sprays, a player icon, and a new epic skin: NANO COLA D.VA!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When you’re not playing to win, you can watch sponsored Twitch broadcasters to unlock even more D.Va-themed sprays!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about D.Va’s Nano Cola Challenge, click &lt;a href=&#34;https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/news/22380666&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August28_herogallery_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Hero Gallery&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August28_herogallery_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented flavor descriptions from displaying when a skin was selected&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented hero descriptions from displaying in the Hero Gallery&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented cosmetics’ unlock requirements from displaying in the Hero Gallery&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August28_heroes_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Heroes&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August28_heroes_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented some of Roadhog’s voice lines from playing with his Lacrosse skin equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Symmetra’s Sentry Turrets to fall through the environment when thrown into a Teleporter&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Symmetra to teleport players into certain vehicles on King’s Row and Numbani&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Winston’s Jump Pack damage to not falloff properly&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August28_sound_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Sound&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August28_sound_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented sound from playing after a memory-intensive team fight&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-50148"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Patch 1.27.0.1</title>
    <updated>2018-08-09T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-08-09:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class=&#34;HeadingBanner&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/j4/J4HEPWP3RVQR1533749413102.jpg);&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;HeadingBanner-header&#34;&gt;AUGUST 9, 2018&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Get ready to kick it, the Summer Games are back!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year Lúcioball makes its way to Busan Stadium, and your heroes are ready to soak in the sun with some new skins! Over the last few months I’ve had the pleasure of working with professional artists around the world to bring these seasonal skins to life.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s a really fun process. It starts with our concept artists sharing their ideas early, which helps hype us up as we start to think of all of the possibilities and details we can add to the models and textures for the final skins, such as making the propellers on the back of D.Va’s Waverunner mech spin faster when she uses her Boosters ability. The 3D artists then choose which skins they want to create and are encouraged to voice their opinions and ideas during the development process so we can help them turn their vision into a reality. Once they have collaborated with us on the digital sculpture and the final in-game model, we then finalize the skins and give them an extra coat of polish in-house with our rigging and skinning, visual effects, audio, and quality assurance testing teams to make sure that they work in-game. The entire effort can take weeks to create a legendary skin, but the end result is always worth it!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This event was especially memorable for me since I got to work with and help train a new artist on our art pipeline. In addition to keeping the process organized and efficient, I also got to get my hands dirty by creating Hana’s model for the D.Va Waveracer skin.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Part of the excitement during the creation process is imagining how fans will receive our artwork—we really hope that you love these skins, and we’re looking forward to reading and hearing what you have to say about them and Summer Games!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;—John Gotch, Senior Character Artist Supervisor&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Summer Games 2018&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/u3/U3J6SNXQK9F21533749771241.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Summer Games return for more fun in the sun! This year, we&#39;re celebrating the spirit of competition with a new Lúcioball arena, Season 2 of Copa Lúcioball, and a smörgåsbord of loot. Unlock over 50 new seasonal items—including legendary skins like Waveracer D.Va, Fastball Zenyatta, and Cabana Ana—alongside our growing collection of summer gear from previous years.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Summer Games, click &lt;a href=&#34;http://playoverwatch.com/en-us/events/summer-games/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;GENERAL UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Changed the name of Junkrat’s Buccaneer skin to Bilgerat&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added under attack voice lines for Zenyatta, Lúcio, and Moria&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;All Overwatch League skins now include the name of the team’s city or state&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Looking for Group&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Settings will be saved after changing filters on the Looking for Group browse screen&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Hero Gallery&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added a What’s New option that displays new unlockable content&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments:&lt;/strong&gt; These changes remove the need to immediately reload after certain long duration ultimates.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Some ultimate abilities now restore ammunition after completion for some heroes&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abilities affected:&lt;/strong&gt; Genji’s Dragonblade, Junkrat’s RIP-Tire, Pharah’s Barrage, Roadhog’s Whole Hog, and Zenyatta’s Transcendence, Winston’s Primal Rage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Ana&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/xl/XL6RBC3KRLAQ1527630418946.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; These changes help Ana’s Nano Boost be usable in more situations. Previously it was almost entirely used to combo with other allies’ ultimates, just before they use them. With this change Nano Boost can now alternatively be used to save an ally from near death in the middle of a big fight.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;ana&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Nano Boost&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now also instantly heals the target for 300 health&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Range increased from 30 to 40 meters&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Brigitte&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/bw/BWLZGE8PVBJI1527630462150.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; Brigitte’s Shield Bash is one of her strongest abilities, and its short cooldown can make it difficult to play against. Slightly increasing its cooldown will give her opponents more opportunity to play around it. We’ve also added an option to control Brigitte’s Repair Pack targeting sensitivity which will allow players to reduce the width of the search angle for the ability. This is useful for trying to target specific allies in the middle of a fight at the cost of making it a bit harder to target allies in general.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;brigitte&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Shield Bash&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cooldown increased from 6 to 7 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Repair Pack&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;An option to control Brigitte’s Repair Pack targeting sensitivity has been added under Options &amp;gt; Controls &amp;gt; Brigitte&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Doomfist&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/7c/7C4LVDIF8ZX21529967875652.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; These changes are just quality of life improvements for how Doomfist interacts with Symmetra’s placed objects.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;doomfist&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Rocket Punch&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No longer impacts Symmetra’s teleporter&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now destroys Symmetra’s sentry turrets without stopping his movement&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Hanzo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/xg/XGT5GAJ80Y7J1527630505280.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; Hanzo’s Lunge ability allows him to be a bit too evasive, so we’re increasing the cooldown to make him easier to catch.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;hanzo&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Lunge&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cooldown increased from 4 to 5 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Lúcio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/2c/2CN0FG5SGPF21533749491730.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; Increasing the amount of shield health gained from Lúcio’s Sound Barrier should make it more effective against incoming burst damage. As part of his last rework, Crossfade’s radius was heavily reduced, but its potency was increased to compensate. While the change was better for him overall, the radius was small enough that it was often difficult to keep his allies in range during a fight, even if they felt reasonably close together. The increased radius should help in these situations.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;lucio&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Crossfade&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Aura radius increase from 10 to 12 meters&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Sound Barrier&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Temporary shields granted increased from 500 to 750&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Mercy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/bh/BH0QKJS7AIJG1533749563007.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; Mercy’s previous healing output made her nearly irreplaceable in any team composition. Even after this change she will still be able to deliver more healing over the course of a match than any other support hero, but it should allow for other healers to be more viable.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;mercy&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Caduceus Staff&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Healing beam reduced from 60 healing per second to 50 healing per second&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Moira&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/mh/MH8K9AL2ZVBU1533749637574.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; This change should help Moira in situations where there are no enemies within reach but your team still requires a lot of healing. She will still need to drain enemies to be fully effective, but this just helps her a bit in the rare cases where there is an extended long-range fight that she can’t reasonably take part in.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;moira&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Biotic Grasp&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Passive energy regeneration rate increased from 2 per second to 2.4 per second&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Reinhardt&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/oh/OHE7FR3IMSFZ1533749721401.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; By smoothing out Reinhardt’s Barrier Field, he now will be able to consistently block enemy abilities and projectiles that could sometimes unintentionally sneak through (e.g. Junkrat’s grenades).&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;reinhardt&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Barrier Field&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Decorative insignia no longer protrudes from the shield’s surface&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Sombra&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/9c/9C8HJQ5KWXS91532451166817.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; The head changes are mostly a bug fix, as her head hit volume was abnormally large, especially from behind. Previously if you fired at her from behind near her upper spine, you could land a head shot. Now her head volume is much more accurate.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;sombra&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;General&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reduced the size of Sombra’s head hit volume&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Symmetra&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/pt/PT31K4K5FMTD1529967943098.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; Symmetra’s primary fire has huge damage potential but it is too difficult to charge because of its low range and slow charge rate. We’re increasing the range to see how it plays out, giving her more opportunities to use it, especially against enemy barriers.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;symmetra&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Photon Projector&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Primary fire range increased from 10 to 12&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Widowmaker&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/y5/Y53MJB70RQYS1533749821829.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; The increased cooldown of Widowmaker&#39;s Grappling Hook will slightly reduce the frequency that she can reposition herself. This allows her to be threatened more easily by agile enemy heroes such as Winston and Genji.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;widowmaker&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Grappling Hook&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cooldown increased from 8 seconds to 10 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Zarya&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/di/DIT7MGCJOE5S1533749866753.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; The smaller radius on Graviton Surge makes it more reasonable for her enemies to try countering it by staying spread out, as well as putting more focus on Zarya to position the ultimate correctly to impact the most players possible. However, the intent of these changes isn’t to lessen Zarya’s overall power significantly so we’re reducing her energy drain rate, which should keep her energy higher on average resulting in more damage and quicker ultimate charge times. Overall, this takes some power out of her ultimate and distributes it else ware to add more counter play against her.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;zarya&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Energy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Drain rate reduced from 2 energy per second to 1.6 energy per second&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Graviton Surge&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Radius reduced from 8 to 6 meters&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;GAME BROWSER AND CUSTOM GAMES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Heroes&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Brigitte’s Repair Pack now has a minimum cooldown time of 1.5 seconds regardless of custom game settings&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August9_General_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August9_General_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that displayed an inaccurate AFK countdown timer before removing players from a match if they were flagged as AFK more than once&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the player camera to display an odd location before switching to the first-person view of the selected hero after Assemble Your Team phase ends&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August9_ai_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;AI&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August9_ai_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Torbjörn bot to fire his gun endlessly if his turret is teleported by a Symmetra player&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August9_competitiveplay_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Competitive Play&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August9_competitiveplay_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that could cause players to lose an endorsement level if they exited before a match completes, but after the return timer for a leaving player has expired&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_heroes_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Heroes&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_heroes_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brigitte&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed projectiles and splash damage to penetrate Brigitte’s Barrier Shield while dashing with the ability&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;D.Va&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused D.Va’s Light Gun to disappear if Roadhog used Chain Hook on her while she used an emote&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Genji&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a visual issue that prevented Genji’s Shuriken ammunition from displaying the correct number briefly after activating Dragonblade&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Genji’s arms to detach from his body if he looked straight down a wall while climbing over edges&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hanzo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Hanzo’s arms to detach from his body if he looked straight down a wall while climbing over edges&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junkrat&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that refilled Junkrat’s ammo if RIP-Tire failed to cast&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that refilled Junkrat&#39;s ammo if he attempted to use RIP-Tire while airborne&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lúcio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Lúcio to gain ultimate charge while Sound Barrier was active if he got hacked&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Orisa&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the health bar on Orisa’s Protective Barrier to disappear when she used Supercharger&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reinhardt&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented cracks from appearing on Reinhardt’s Overwatch League Away skins when his Barrier Field takes damage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Roadhog&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Roadhog’s Chain Hook from retracting to his hand if he is interrupted mid-cast&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sombra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Sombra’s visual effects to display darker than intended&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Sombra to destroy her Translocator after teleporting to it&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Sombra’s Translocator to bleed when struck by enemy players&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tracer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Tracer’s Pulse Bombs to stick onto the wrong side of shields when the targeted enemy moved quickly&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wrecking Ball&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Wrecking Ball from using sprays when in Roll form&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Piledriver to displace Mei while she is in Cryo-freeze&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zarya&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Zarya’s Graviton Surge visual effects to extend beyond the ability’s radius&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August9_herogallery_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Hero Gallery&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August9_herogallery_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented rotating hero models while viewed in the Hero Gallery when equipped with Overwatch League skins&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the Communication Wheel from functioning when equipping a spray, voice line, or emote from a Loot Box&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August9_lookingforgroup_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Looking for Group&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August9_lookingforgroup_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused some groups to be unable to queue for a game mode&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August9_maps_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Maps&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;August9_maps_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eichenwalde&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Eichenwalde’s castle gate to falls into the ground when destroyed by the payload&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-49656"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Patch 1.26.0.3</title>
    <updated>2018-07-24T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-07-24:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeadingBanner&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/za/ZAZFRW6DLU201532451117619.jpg);&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;HeadingBanner-header&#34;&gt;JULY 24, 2018&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Look out world, Wrecking Ball’s here!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our smallest hero has become one of our team&#39;s biggest achievements. When we first introduced Wrecking Ball to the team, making the hamster hero fit in the &lt;em&gt;Overwatch&lt;/em&gt; lineup presented an exciting challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Exploration is the key to animation, so we tried many different personality iterations for the hamster. At first, we made him maniacal, but he felt too evil, so we tried instead to highlight the difference between Hammond the critter—cute, cuddly, mischievous—and the Wrecking Ball mech—powerful, imposing, cold, and impersonal. Our eureka moment was nailing his “Relaxed” emote; I feel like it captures Hammond’s character and personality perfectly. He exudes confidence with the way he shifts his weight in the seat to get comfortable, then throws a cheese puff into the air and catches it in his mouth. After seeing it, we knew we has something special.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wrecking Ball is one of our most agile tank heroes so far and has unique mechanics that I haven’t seen in other games. It was so exciting to see how much people loved him when we finally announced him. Be sure to roll into a match as Wrecking Ball and, while you’re at it, check out how he uses his trackball to pilot the mech!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;—Ryan Denniston, Lead Animator&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;New Hero: Wrecking Ball (Tank):&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/e1/E1FN1QR64PXV1532463369144.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wrecking Ball’s tinkering capabilities and iron-clad mech make him a formidable tank hero, capable of bowling through the front line of the opposition and causing mayhem in the back line. His primary weapon, &lt;strong&gt;Quad Cannons&lt;/strong&gt;, are two sets of twin machine guns that shred enemies caught in their crosshairs. No team is too much for Wrecking Ball to engage against with his &lt;strong&gt;Adaptive Shield&lt;/strong&gt;, which generates more health based on the number of enemies nearby. This shield makes him incredibly difficult to kill when he bulldozes into the fray and, once he starts to get low on health, also provides him the endurance to escape. The &lt;strong&gt;Roll&lt;/strong&gt; ability allows Wrecking Ball to withdraw the mech’s robotic limbs, transforming it into a ball with increased movement speed. No obstacle can stand in Wrecking Ball’s way when he uses &lt;strong&gt;Grappling Claw&lt;/strong&gt;, a short-range ability that grips the environment, letting him swing across terrain gaps or around corners to smash enemies. Grappling Claw also allows Wrecking Ball to reach top speed and ram into foes, dealing destructive damage and knocking them back. While airborne, the mech’s &lt;strong&gt;Piledriver&lt;/strong&gt; ability causes Wrecking Ball to slam down from the air and knock his enemies off their feet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When Wrecking Ball is at his strongest, he can use &lt;strong&gt;Minefield&lt;/strong&gt; which flings mines onto the ground that deal a considerable amount of damage to enemies unfortunate enough to trigger them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Wrecking Ball, click here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As with all new heroes, please note that Wrecking Ball&#39;s release in Competitive Play will be delayed by two weeks.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;GENERAL UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added a note to Sombra’s Hero Information page about her ability to remove her own Translocator&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Removed the Shield Generators Destroyed statistic from players’ Career Profiles&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Looking for Group&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added a button that allows you to queue into the selected game mode once the group becomes full&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added a button to relist groups in the LFG browser when the group has empty role slots&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments:&lt;/strong&gt; The goal of these changes is to slightly reduce the impact of damage falloff on mid-range weapons. While assessing falloff mechanics across the board, weapons intended primarily for close-range combat benefited too greatly from lowering their falloff restrictions. We also normalized a couple of outliers in that Mei had a long-range travel time projectile with falloff applied and Widowmaker&#39;s automatic fire did not have any.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Several heroes have received major changes to their damage falloff:&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Bastion&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Configuration: Sentry and Configuration: Recon - Minimum damage at max range increased from 30% to 50%.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;McCree&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Peacekeeper - Minimum damage at max range increased from 30% to 50%&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mei&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Endothermic Blaster - Removed all damage falloff from her secondary fire projectile&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Soldier: 76&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Heavy Pulse Rifle - Minimum damage at max range increased from 30% to 50%&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Widowmaker&#xA;&#x9;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Widow&#39;s Kiss - Now has damage falloff applied on her automatic primary fire (50% at max range)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Hanzo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/xg/XGT5GAJ80Y7J1527630505280.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; Hanzo’s new kit has proven to be a bit too powerful, especially his new Storm Arrows ability. We’re lowering the frequency that he can have this ability available to make it more reasonable to play around.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;hanzo&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Storm Arrows&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Duration reduced from 6 to 5 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cooldown increased from 8 to 10 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Sombra&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/9c/9C8HJQ5KWXS91532451166817.png&#34;/&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; These changes allow Sombra to more easily play as an infiltrator and scout for her team, as well as give her time to pick and choose when to reveal herself to ambush her enemies.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;a class=&#34;Tooltip-handle Tooltip-handle--text&#34; data-tooltip=&#34;mccree&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Stealth&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now lasts indefinitely&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No longer can contest objectives while invisible&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Movement speed buff decreased from +70% to +50%&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Translocator&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now lasts indefinitely&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Can now be destroyed (has 5 health)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Radius reduced&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;MAP UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;MAP UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments:&lt;/strong&gt; In a previous patch we added a system to adjust the respawn rate of defenders in situations where attackers have a prolonged advantage in fights on final objectives. We’re just making this system a bit more aggressive to further reduce the duration of the long, drawn out fights that can occur when the defender spawns are so close to the action.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;When final objectives on non-control maps are contested for extended amounts of time and attackers have an advantage in numbers, the respawn time for defenders now increases even faster&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Assault Maps&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments:&lt;/strong&gt; We have reduced the overall game time for Assault maps in Quickplay and Arcade Modes. Players now have four minutes to capture each point instead of the current five minutes per point. In some games, Point A would be captured rather quickly resulting in what could be lengthy battle over Point B. Point B is typically more defendable than Point A and, in some games, defenders were able to hold for the entire duration of remaining time which could potentially be 8 minutes or more. We felt that in these instances the overall time was simply too long for either team, with attackers unable to take the point and defenders having to hold. The reduction in time is now consistent with the Competitive Play times which provides an ample amount of time for both attackers and defenders, but hopefully removes the occasional game where it feels like you are playing against the timer and not the other team.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Objective time reduced from 5 minutes to 4 minutes per control point in Quick Play and Arcade modes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_General_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_General_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the group leader’s UI to appear that they’re canceling or leaving Waiting for Players when using a controller&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from receiving an AFK warning for not moving after receiving the No XP warning for not being in combat&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Competitive Elimination to display as your last match played in the Recent Players menu&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players added to Avoid as Teammate from being removed if that player was added to their friends list&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_ai_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;AI&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_ai_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Torbjörn bot to continuously try upgrading his turret when placed in an inaccessible location&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_customgame_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Custom Game&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_customgame_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented groups electing to spectate from being placed into the Spectator section of the Custom Game they’re trying to watch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_endorsements_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Endorsements&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_endorsements_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the Team Information screen to display an Endorsement level of a player who left the game&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the Endorsement input from opening the Endorsement tray if it shared that input with another input&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the Nearby Players menu from displaying Endorsement levels&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the text for the Sportsmanship Endorsement to bleed outside the chat box&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_GamebrowserCustomGames_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Game Browser &amp;amp; Custom Games&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_GamebrowserCustomGames_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed heroes to deploy multiple barriers or turrets when a decreased cooldown modifier was applied in a Custom Game&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused players to sometimes spawn into a wall or floor when playing a Deathmatch Custom Game with Respawn as Random Hero enabled&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_heroes_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Heroes&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_heroes_bugs;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented heroes from playing a hit reaction animation when shot&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ana&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Ana’s Naptime achievement from being granted when interrupting Moira’s Coalescence&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Ana’s Sleep Dart effect to persist on afflicted targets after changing heroes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brigitte&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Brigitte from dashing forward when using Shield Bash if she was airborne due to Doomfist’s Rising Uppercut&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Brigitte’s portrait to show a non-existent ponytail with her Shieldmaiden skin equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doomfist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Rocket Punch to stop if he hit Symmetra’s Turret when it was in midair&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Meteor Strike from hitting Reinhardt if he faced his Field Barrier upward&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug with Doomfist’s Rocket Punch that prevented it from canceling Genji’s Cyber-agility, Lúcio’s Wall Ride, or Hanzo’s Wall Climb on impact&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Meteor Strike impact visual effect from occurring&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist to plummet to his death if he used Meter Strike in the basement of the Château Guillard Deathmatch map&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;D.Va&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented D.Va’s mech rear hatch from connecting to her mech when viewing D.Va’s Peace Victory Pose.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Genji&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Genji’s kneepad to clip into his legs when wearing his Classic skin&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Genji’s knees to pop while shifting his weight during his idle animation in the Hero Gallery&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hanzo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes caused Hanzo’s Dragonstrike projectile to fire backward&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junkrat&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Junkrat’s Frag Launcher grenades from dealing the correct amount of damage on direct hits&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Junkrat to set multiple Steel Traps in Custom Games&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented teammates from viewing Junkrat’s respawn timer if he died while piloting RIP-Tire&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed the player to move the camera when Junkrat’s RIP-Tire was frozen&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Junkrat’s Frag Launcher grenades to get stuck in certain terrain&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mei&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mei’s Ice Wall to be destroyed if Sombra hacked her&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mercy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mercy&#39;s Cadeceus Staff and Cadeceus Blaster to appear missing when using quick melee and weapon swap simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Mercy to damage boost certain abilities (e.g. Hanzo’s Dragonstrike, D.Va’s Self-Destruct, and Junkrat’s Steel Trap)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moira&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Moira’s Healing Orb from healing friendly training bots in the Practice Range&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Moira’s Biotic Orbs from trigging controller vibration when using a controller&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reinhardt&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Reinhardt’s Charge from propelling him forward if he was airborne due to Doomfist’s Rising Uppercut&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Roadhog&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Roadhog’s Chain Hook target to be pulled to his new location when he used Symmetra’s Teleporter&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sombra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Sombra to push and contest payloads while invisible&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused parts of Sombra’s Translocator to be invulnerable&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Sombra to reach unintended locations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Symmetra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s Turrets from displaying a red outline when viewed by the enemy team&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Reinhardt’s Earthshatter to sometimes go through Symmetra’s Photon Barrier&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s Teleporter from using visual effects with her Oasis skin equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Symmetra to receive credit toward her Huge Success achievement if she teleported her Sentry Turrets&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s Photon Barrier from destroying existing ones when placing a new one in Deathmatch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Symmetra’s Sentry Turrets to shoot enemies through walls when placed on uneven surfaces&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Symmetra’s Teleport telegraph to cancel if she fell off a ledge while placing it&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tracer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Tracer to gain capture point progress during her Recall ability&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zarya&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Zarya’s Particle Cannon from gaining energy when attacked by an enemy Symmetra or Zarya if they were too close to her when she used Particle Barrier&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Widowmaker&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Widowmaker from grappling to some walls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_lookingforgroup_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Looking for Group&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_lookingforgroup_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused all game modes to be selectable when adding a player to a group&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the Choose Roles menu from offering a default role when accessed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from receiving messaging notifying them why they were unable to change a Looking for Group title if they were suspended from changing Custom Game names&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented role icons from displaying on hero portraits&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed two players were able to queue for the same Looking for Group spot&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_maps_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Maps&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;July24_maps_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junkertown&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Junker Queen’s voice lines from playing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-49154"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Patch 1.25.0.1</title>
    <updated>2018-06-26T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-06-26:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class=&#34;HeadingBanner&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/ix/IX5ATWCIEFOS1529962558017.jpg);&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;HeadingBanner-header&#34;&gt;JUNE 26, 2018&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re super excited about this patch because we are adding some social features that we hope you guys really like!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, our Endorsement system. Endorsements give you a way to acknowledge other players for having a positive impact on your gaming experience. We have ways to report people for poor conduct, but now, if you have teammates who coordinated well, a leader who gave great direction, or even someone who was just being positive you can now let them know how much you appreciated it with an endorsement!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Second is Looking for Group. A long-awaited feature that we’ve being dying to get in the game. Looking for group allows you to find like-minded players before you queue to make sure you have the kind of Overwatch experience you want! Things like specifying what game mode want to play, preferring voice chat, and knowing that a player wants to play a certain role before you go into battle together goes a long way toward solid hero compositions and team work. One small tip: Once you have created a LFG group you can browse the list and search for groups that meet your needs and invite them to join up! This is a more proactive approach to getting a group together faster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We can’t wait for you guys to start using these systems!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;—Jeremy Craig, Principal Game Designer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Endorsements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/tm/TMGNJRTM03J01529962538076.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Acknowledge your fellow Overwatch players’ positivity with &lt;a href=&#34;http://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/endorsements/&#34;&gt;endorsements&lt;/a&gt;! Recognize commendable behavior for players exhibiting sportsmanship, being a good teammate, or for shot calling. Commend players who lead you to victory, put the team’s needs above their own, or exhibit humility in victory or grace in defeat. Endorsements are readily available to view on Career Profiles, the Groups menu, and more so you can tell at a glance the types of players you’re playing with. Those who consistently maintain a high endorsement level will receive periodic rewards, while those who display negative behavior or accrue suspensions will lose their endorsements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Looking for Group&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/3g/3GQ8V2FMBVAP1529962572415.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Play your way using the Looking for Group feature! You can control your gameplay experience before stepping into a match by using specific parameters to create your dream team. Join a team of other like-minded players or lead a group of your own by creating a group with your personal preferences such as game mode, role enforcement, and more. Those who want to queue up for Quick Play, Play vs AI, or any competitive mode can set the types of roles others can play. These specifications will then be activated in-game (e.g. players who chose a support role will be restricted to only using heroes in that category).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;GENERAL UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments:&lt;/strong&gt; &#34;Since the line between Offense and Defense heroes has become increasingly blurred, we’ve decided to group all those heroes into a single new “Damage” category. We believe that the term more closely matches the role name that is now being used in Overwatch League and across most of the game’s community.&#34;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;All heroes in the Defense and Offense categories have been merged into a new category: Damage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Combat can now be heard 25% further away&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Changed the name of the Varok spray to Saurfang&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[PC] Players must have Blizzard SMS Protect enabled on their account to be eligible for the Top 500&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Acknowledge and Interact buttons are now separate input bindings&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Career Profile&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added an Inspire Uptime Percentage statistic for Brigitte on the Career Profile&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Removed some statistics for Symmetra on the Career Profile&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added a Scoped Critical Hit Accuracy statistic for Widowmaker on the Career Profile&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Career Profiles will no longer be public by default (now defaults to Friends Only). An option to make Career Profiles visible has been added under Options &amp;gt; Social &amp;gt; Profile Visibility&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;ARCADE UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Symmetra can now be played in 1v1 duel game modes (e.g. 1v1 Limited Duel and 1v1 Mystery Duel)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Doomfist&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/7c/7C4LVDIF8ZX21529967875652.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; The increased movement speed on Meteor Strike gives Doomfist new options in how and where to deploy it. His passive is also being increased, allowing him to survive more often when diving into enemies.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Meteor Strike&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Bonus movement speed increased from 150% to 200%&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;The Best Defense…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Shield gain increased from 30 to 35 for normal abilities&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;McCree&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/kv/KVBH6MG8C5N91529967905889.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; While McCree’s Deadeye rarely came into play at 70 meters, we are increasing the range so it cannot be a limiting factor during normal gameplay.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Deadeye&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Range increased from 70 meters to 200 meters&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IcoHeading-text&#34;&gt;Orisa&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/3f/3FE4LV1S3UGO1529967929720.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; Supercharger wasn’t getting enough use, considering its impact. This change allows Orisa to use her ultimate more aggressively, knowing that she will be able to generate them more easily.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Supercharger&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ultimate cost reduced by 15%&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader HeroHeader--raised&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;HeroHeader-text&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Symmetra&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;HeroHeader-image&#34; src=&#34;https://bnetcmsus-a.akamaihd.net/cms/page_media/pt/PT31K4K5FMTD1529967943098.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;CalloutBox CalloutBox--attached&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments&lt;/strong&gt; The goal of these changes is to move Symmetra to her new damage role and make her more flexible and viable across more areas of the game than she was previously. Now that Symmetra is no longer a support hero, she is expected to be able to dish out heavy damage, and these changes allow for her to do so. She should be more powerful and interesting in more team compositions and maps, and she should also be stronger on offense and defense.&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Photon Projector&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No longer locks onto targets&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Range increased to 10 meters&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Damage ramping now takes 2 seconds per damage level instead of 1 second&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Damage ramp increased from 30/60/120 to 60/120/180&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now generates ammo instead of spending it when hitting a barrier&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ammo reduced from 100 to 70&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Alternate Fire&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No longer pierces targets&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now explodes on contact&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Projectile speed increased&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Charge up speed increased&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Damage changed to 60 impact / 60 explosive&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Sentry Turret&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Turret is now placed like a projectile instead of being set in place&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Can hold a max of 3, down from 6&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Can now deploy a max 3, down from 6&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Damage increased&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Amount of slowing effect increased&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;Teleporter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Can now place the exit up to 25 meters away from Symmetra&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Entrance will automatically be built in front of Symmetra, rather than at her team’s spawn point&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lasts 10 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Health lowered to 300&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;More things can teleport through it (e.g. Junkrat’s RIP-Tire)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Entrance can be destroyed&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If either the entrance or exit is destroyed, the other is removed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;IconHeading&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;IconHeading-text&#34;&gt;New Ultimate: Photon Barrier&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Deploys a barrier that is big enough to span and cut through an entire map&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Orientation can be changed by pressing the ultimate button again&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lasts 15 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Has 5000 health&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;MAP UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Horizon Lunar Colony&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Quote&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments:&lt;/strong&gt; We’ve wanted to make some gameplay improvements to Horizon Lunar Colony for some time now. The defenders’ spawn room had a problem with its main exit that allowed defenders to quickly duck back inside and regain health while attackers shot at them without doing damage. Since we were already reworking the entire back area, we decided to make some more changes addressing player feedback. The idea behind the rework of Point A was to not only help the defenders a bit, but also provide some gameplay options aside from sitting on the point and trying to hold it for as long as possible. Easier access to high ground, as well as limiting the routes for attackers (or at least allowing for defenders to more easily spot the attackers), will allow more opportunity for counters and create a better gameplay experience.&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ve made a lot of additions and changes to the art throughout the map for you to discover as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point A&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added a staircase on the right when exiting the Hydroponics Room&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Removed the door to the lower room on the right&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Removed the small wall on the catwalk above Point A&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added some cover walls to the catwalk area&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Moved the door next to the staircase that led to Winston’s room&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The door is now on the side of the wall in the training pit&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Moved the large health pack to the back of the room&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Removed some clutter in the upper left computer room&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hydroponics Room&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Switched the positions of the large and small health pack&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Changed some of the hydroponic plant cover on the right&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point B&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Defender spawn room exits moved from the front to the sides out of direct line of fire&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Small rooms added at spawn room exits&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Additional cover added near the spawn room exits&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added a route and larger platform leading to the back right corner&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Raised the platform to the same height as the attackers’ platform on the opposite side of the point&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The location of the old defender exit is now an alcove with a small health pack&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Both teams can still pass behind the point, but there is now a cut-through in the middle of the wall for better access&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The area above the window overlooking the point is now covered&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A large platform with cover has been attached to the left side of the catwalk&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The upper platform for the attackers has been reduced&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The doorway leading to the platform is slightly smaller&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;UnderlinedHeader&#34;&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;June26_General_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;General&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;June26_General_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented loading screens from displaying the game mode&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the capture point UI to display capture progress as 100% before the point was captured&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused some sprays to be pixelated&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;June26_ai_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;AI&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;June26_ai_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Sombra bot to continue hacking health packs if the ability was disabled in a Custom Game&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;June26_heroes_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Heroes&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;June26_heroes_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ana&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Ana’s Naptime achievement from being granted when interrupting Moira’s Coalescence&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Ana’s Sleep Dart effect to persist on afflicted targets after changing heroes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bastion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented McCree’s Flashbang from interrupting Bastion’s Configuration: Tank transformation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Bastion’s treads to disfigure if he was frozen while in Tank configuration&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brigitte&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Junkrat’s grenades to damage Brigitte when hitting her Barrier Shield&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Brigitte’s Barrier Shield to become indestructible if her Barrier Shield Cooldown Time modifier was set to 0% in a Custom Game&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Brigitte’s Rocket Flail to clip into the ground during her Flail highlight intro on King’s Row&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Brigitte to proc Inspire when hitting gondola omnics with her Rocket Flail in Rialto&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Brigitte to proc Inspire by hitting the motorcycle in the Junkertown attacker spawn room&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Brigitte to use Shield Bash while affected by Steel Trap or Graviton Surge&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Brigitte’s Inspire passive from sometimes healing allies out of line of sight&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Brigitte’s knee pad and foot to clip the ground during her Kneel victory pose when wearing her Paladin or Engineer skins&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Brigitte’s arm animation to shake when using Repair Pack and Rally in quick succession&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doomfist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Meteor Strike animation to place him back on the ground when used in midair&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Meteor Strike cooldown UI from being hidden if he died during its activation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the HUD messaging for Doomfist’s Meteor Strike to indicate that players can zoom their camera out&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Rocket Punch from dealing bonus damage when the target hit a friendly Mei’s Ice Wall&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Doomfist’s Rocket Punch bonus damage to hit Genji after using Swift Strike to move through the punch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Rocket Punch’s bonus damage from applying if the enemy used an evasive ability at the same time they hit a wall (e.g. Moira’s Fade, Tracer’s Blink, or Reaper’s Wraith Form)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented Doomfist’s Rocket Punch from impacting some walls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Rocket Punch, Rising Uppercut, and Seismic Slam from not playing the appropriate sound effect if these abilities were disabled or on cooldown&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented enemies struck by Doomfist’s Rocket Punch from taking additional collision damage when hitting Mei’s Cryo-freeze&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Rising Uppercut animation from playing when used after hitting something with Rocket Punch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Doomfist to use Seismic Slam and escape Graviton Surge when within range&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s failed Seismic Slams to display the wrong UI information&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Seismic Slam from being usable if spammed in a Custom Game with 0% cooldown modifier&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;D.Va&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused D.Va’s mech to do a standing pose right before detonating&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug prevented the South Korean flag decal from displaying when she was in her mech&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug prevented projectiles from hitting D.Va if she stood behind her mech after it detonated&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the Team Kill sound effects from playing for D.Va inside her mech&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed pilot D.Va could summon extra, empty mechs if she used Call Mech while standing on top of an enemy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed D.Va to activate her mech boosters after activating her Self-Destruct&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Genji&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Genji’s Swift Strike to do damage after he dies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented stuns from applying if Genji used Swift Strike&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Genji to wall climb while using emotes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hanzo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[PS4] Fixed a bug that prevented Hanzo’s belt tassels from animating with his Young Hanzo or Young Master skin equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Hanzo’s Storm Bow projectiles to sometimes use the sound effect for Storm Arrow&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Hanzo to wall climb while using emotes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Hanzo’s Dragon Strike animation from playing if he was in a Graviton Surge&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junkrat&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Junkrat to place multiple Steel Traps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Junkrat’s projectiles to become invisible if they were shot through railings&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the medal in Junkrat’s Medal victory pose to clip through his chin with his Scarecrow or Hayseed skins equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused turrets to target Junkrat’s Concussion Mines while airborne&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lúcio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Lúcio from using his Sonic Amplifier when waving hello&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Lucio from using Soundwave if he had zero ammo&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;McCree&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented McCree’s Flashbang from giving credit for environmental kills&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused McCree’s Deadeye targeting markers to persist if the target died while it was active&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused McCree’s Deadeye reticle to lock onto players who die while the ability was active&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the tumbleweed from appearing in McCree’s The Duel highlight intro&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mei&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Mei from receiving environmental kill credit if her targets were frozen&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mei’s projectiles to appear that they weren’t passing through friendly barriers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mercy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Mercy’s Caduceus Blaster and Caduceus Staff from appearing when switching between weapons and using quick melee at the same time&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mercy’s Caduceus Blaster shots to become invisible if they were deflected by Genji if her Pink skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Mercy’s Guardian Angel cooldown from resetting if Valkyrie was used midflight&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the cooldown on Mercy’s Guardian Angel from being refunded while Valkyrie was active&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the resolution quality of Mercy’s Today’s Top 5 highlights icon to drop with her Zhuque skin equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented player names from displaying when being healed by Mercy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Mercy to see her eliminated teammates while resurrecting a target&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Mercy to switch weapons while using her Caduceus emote&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moira&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Moira’s Biotic Grasp from damaging barriers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Moira’s Biotic Grasp’s beam to disappear when attaching to barriers from certain angles&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from receiving the Excuse Me achievement when successfully interrupting Moira’s Coalescence&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Moira’s Biotic Grasp to heal targets behind an enemy barrier&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Moira’s Biotic Orb to pass through breakable objects&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Moira’s Biotic Grasp to attach onto the base of targets (e.g. Mei’s Cryo-freeze)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Orisa&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from being awarded Orisa’s Halt State achievement&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Orisa’s Fusion Driver from closing if her Halt projectile was affected by Defense Matrix or Deflect immediately after it spawned&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug where Orisa’s arm would clip into her leg during her Puppy emote&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the effect of Orisa’s Halt! to persist if Wraith Form or Fade were used immediately after being pulled in&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pharah&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Pharah from being knocked back by her Concussive Blast in spawn rooms&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reaper&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug with Reaper’s Shadow Step sound effect continuously playing while moving around on breakable terrain in Petra.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reinhardt&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Reinhardt’s Barrier Field from not playing the correct sound effect if it was affected by Sombra’s Hack&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Reinhardt’s Barrier Field cooldown to cancel an active hammer swing when it became ready to use&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Reinhardt’s Rocket Hammer eliminations from receiving credit in the Kill Feed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reaper&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug with Reaper’s Shadow Step sound effect continuously playing while moving around on breakable terrain in Petra&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Roadhog&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Roadhog’s Chain Hook to reel in targets even if the ability was interrupted&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sombra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Sombra’s Hack from interrupting Symmetra’s Teleporter placement&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug caused Sombra’s Hack to be interrupted by thin environment objects (e.g. lamp posts)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Sombra’s Translocator from being destroyed when it was thrown off a level&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Symmetra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s Photon Barrier from blocking Reinhardt’s Earthshatter&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Symmetra’s Photon Projector to gain charge when used on breakable objects&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s Photon Barrier from being placed with the correct orientation if the player rapidly turned during its placement&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s Photon Barrier from being placed on moving platforms or payloads&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Symmetra to place her Shield Generator inside gates on certain maps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Symmetra to place her Sentry Turrets inside chests and vending machines&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Symmetra’s Sentry Turrets to deploy at maximum range without sticking to a surface&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s Sentry Turrets from dealing the correct amount of damage and slow values&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Symmetra’s Teleporter to self-destruct when it was placed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Torbjörn’s turret from being built on Symmetra’s Teleporter&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s secondary fire from consuming ammo when minimally charged&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s Teleporter from teleporting allies that moved through it at high movement speeds (e.g. Genji’s Swift Strike)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Symmetra’s Teleporter to fall through the ground if placed on platform edges&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s eyes from aligning properly during her Askew and Snowflakes highlight intros with her Dragon skin equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Torbjörn&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Torbjörn’s Batter Up emote from playing sound effects if he switched weapons&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tracer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Tracer’s Pulse Bomb to stick on the opposite side of barriers when thrown at a certain angle&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Tracer’s animation to pause at the start of her Bomb Spin emote&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Widowmaker&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Widowmaker’s shooting animation to become stuck if she scoped while firing and then jumped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug with the grammar in the flavor text for Widowmaker’s Comtesse skin&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Widowmaker’s Venom Mine from being destroyed when thrown over the environment edges on Oasis Gardens&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winston&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug where placing Winston’s Barrier Projector while going a step upwards would cause it to fall through the floor&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zenyatta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Zenyatta’s Discord Orb sound effects from playing with his Cultist skin equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Zenyatta’s arm to clip through his pants during his Heroic highlight intro&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;section class=&#34;Drawer-handle&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-handle&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;June26_maps_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;Maps&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;Drawer-container&#34; data-js=&#34;slideout-container&#34; data-slideout-id=&#34;June26_maps_bugs&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blizzard World&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Soldier: 76’s Helix Rockets and Zarya’s primary fire from popping balloons&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Horizon Lunar Colony&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused armor packs to land behind crates and not be usable&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Petra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented ability indicators for Seismic Slam and Ice Wall from being visible on the breakable terrain in Petra&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Reinhardt’s Earthshatter to travel across holes in the breakable tile floor on Petra&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rialto&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug where heroes would move left and right on their own while standing in one of the speed boats in the canal&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug where players were able to apply a spray on the surface of a body of water&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watchpoint: Gibralter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the first Attacker spawn room to extend past its walls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-47946"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>