<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Overwatch PC Updates</title>
  <id>https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
  <updated>2018-02-08T12:01:28-08:00</updated>
  <subtitle>Patch notes and updates for Overwatch</subtitle>
  <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/"></link>
  <author>
    <name>Blizzard</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – February 8, 2018</title>
    <updated>2018-02-08T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-02-08:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Seasonal Event: Lunar New Year 2018&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Get ready to ring in the Year of the Dog!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year, we’re celebrating Lunar New Year with over 50 new seasonal items including legendary skins like Red Phoenix (Zhu Que) Mercy, Black Tortoise (Xuan Wu) Zarya, White Tiger (Bai Hu) Genji, and Black Lily Widowmaker. Experience our updates to our Capture the Flag mode—including a competitive Capture the Flag mode and Sudden Death—on a brand-new map, Ayutthaya.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about the new Capture the Flag changes, click &lt;a href=&#34;file:///C:/Users/tpowers/AppData/Local/Microsoft/Windows/INetCache/Content.Outlook/CORDLEF7/LINK&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hero Skin Selection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fashion-forward heroes, rejoice! Players can now change hero skins with the “Select Skin” dropdown menu in the Hero Select screen at the start of a match. Show off your favorite unlocked skins when playing solo or coordinate with your friends to be the best dressed on the battlegrounds of tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doomfist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hand Cannon&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Damage reduced from 11 to 6&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Number of bullets fired increased from 6 to 11&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Spread pattern made more consistent&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;We have made a lot of progress with Doomfist’s movement in recent patches but we wanted to revisit his Hand Cannon. While the damage per bullet has been lowered, the number of bullets he fires per Hand Cannon shot has been increased which makes his overall damage output unchanged. Overall, these changes will help his Hand Cannon feel much more consistent.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;USER INTERFACE UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Matchmaking UI now displays the game mode players have queued for while waiting for players&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Competitive Play leaver messages now display as a chat notification&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Hero Select screen now displays the game mode and map type&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Zenyatta’s Orb of Discord and Orb of Harmony will now display its target’s hero name&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the mouse cursor to lose focus when using third party overlays (e.g. Discord)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that sometimes prevented the Overwatch League scheduled matches of the day from loading&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented bots from voting on cards at the end of the match on Hybrid and Control maps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive Play&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented capture progress UI on Assault and Hybrid maps from displaying the correct team colors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed players to use the Hero Select screen during the loading screen at the start of a match&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deathmatch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Widowmaker’s Infra-sight from functioning if it was used at the same time as another Widowmaker’s Infra-sight&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Torbjörn to collide with his turret&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Symmetra’s Sentry Turrets to continue targeting Junkrat’s Steel Trap after it was destroyed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from being able to stand on top of enemy players&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed backfilling players to enter at 9th place during the match&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused targets hacked by Sombra to appear purple instead of red&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the displayed hero on the lobby screen to appear in low detail when entering and exiting the Overwatch League screen&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Game Browser and Custom Games&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed players to summon infinite bots in custom games&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused D.Va to lose her Self-Destruct ultimate if she died out of her mech when the “Spawn with Ultimate Ready” option was enabled&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the Victory voice line to play when a match ended in a draw while spectating&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused airborne heroes to lose speed when changing direction&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented golden weapon visual effects from displaying when an Overwatch League skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused heroes’ scoped shots to be calculated as misses in the accuracy statistic&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Ana’s Candy emote from displaying when viewing Kill Cam footage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Rocket Punch to impact with D.Va’s mech before it materialized during her Call Mech ability&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented kills caused by Doomfist’s Rocket Punch from receiving environmental kill credit&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Genji from sheathing his katana after using his Whirlwind emote&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Genji from using his Cyber-agility occasionally&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Hanzo’s Dragonstrike to be calculated in the accuracy statistic&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Hanzo’s Wall Climb from activating occasionally&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mercy’s Caduceus Staff to disappear when using the Parasol emote&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mercy to fly in an unintended direction if she was stunned during Guardian Angel&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Mercy from destroying breakables she collides with in her flight path when using Guardian Angel&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mercy’s Valkyrie flight controls to not be precise when using Resurrect&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Moira’s Biotic Grasp’s hits against barriers to be calculated as misses in her accuracy statistic&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that extended the cooldown of Orisa’s Halt! by one second if it successfully pulled an enemy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Sombra to block Reaper’s Death Blossom if she used her Marioneta emote&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Reinhardt to have a blank expression during his Toast victory pose&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed projectiles to sometimes penetrate Reinhardt’s Barrier Field&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Reinhardt’s Charge bonus damage from being dealt if the target was sandwiched between a charging friendly Reinhardt and a charging enemy Reinhardt&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Reinhardt to knock back a target instead of pinning them if he collided with an enemy at the start of his Charge&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Roadhog’s canister from appearing when viewing Overwatch League skins&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Roadhog’s Chain Hook to clip the first-person camera when pulling in a target&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Sombra’s EMP from canceling an enemy Sombra’s Hack if it was in progress&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Symmetra’s Shield Generator from displaying in the Overwatch League skin preview screen&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Torbjörn’s lava ball from appearing in his Batter Up emote if his hammer was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Widowmaker’s hair to not hang properly in the Hanging Around Highlight Intro when an Overwatch League skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Widowmaker’s Venom Mine to use Overwatch League team colors when an Overwatch League skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Widowmaker’s Grappling Hook animation from playing when using the ability&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Winston to lose some upward momentum when using Jump Pack off small inclines&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Overwatch League team decals to disappear from Winston’s suit when he used Primal Rage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Zenyatta’s Discord Orb to fly in an odd direction if its target died before arriving&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hero Gallery&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from purchasing non-hero sprays&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused some heroes to get stuck behind the lamp post directly outside the first Defender spawn room in Blizzard World&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that allowed players to reach unintended locations in Blizzard World&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented D.Va’s Micro Missiles from passing through piñatas on Dorado&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Junkrat’s RIP-tire to travel under the trailer at the final point on Hollywood&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Moira’s Biotic Orbs from bouncing off the wooden pillars on Hollywood&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the UI to show a fraction of a meter to go when reaching checkpoints on Escort and Assault/Escort maps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the hero portrait from displaying when watching Highlights when an Overwatch League skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented player portraits from displaying during the Play of the Game, Kill Cam, Spectating, and Highlights&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-43435"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – January 30, 2018</title>
    <updated>2018-01-30T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-01-30:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;World of Warcraft: Battle for Azeroth Pre-purchase Goodies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When you pre-purchase a Digital Deluxe version of World of Warcraft: Battle for Azeroth you’ll receive several Warcraft-themed goodies in Overwatch. Show your faction pride on the battlefields of tomorrow with emotes for Tracer; Horde- and Alliance-themed voice lines for Torbjörn; Anduin, Jaina, Sylvanas, and Saurfang sprays; and Kul Tiras and Zandalar player icons.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To pre-order World of Warcraft: Battle for Azeroth, click &lt;a href=&#34;https://us.shop.battle.net/en-us/product/world-of-warcraft-battle-for-azeroth&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junkrat&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Concussion Mine&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now will deal less damage to targets farther away from the explosion’s center&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Junkrat has been enjoying the flexibility his double-charge Concussion Mine provides, but it has become a bit too easy to throw out huge bursts of damage in a large area. With this change he can still dish out similar damage but he must now be more accurate with his tosses.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mercy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Valkyrie&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No longer makes Resurrect instant&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No longer grants a bonus Resurrect charge&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The speed bonus Guardian Angel receives when activating Valkyrie has been decreased by 50%&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Duration reduced from 20 seconds to 15 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mercy’s recent Resurrect changes have helped in allowing enemies to have more counter play in dealing with her, but she was able to use Resurrect through Valkyrie enough to largely mitigate the impact of the previous changes. Additionally, we’re toning back the amount of mobility Valkyrie provides through Guardian Angel and reducing its duration to overall reduce the power of this ability.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented D.Va’s face and hair textures from loading when her Black Cat skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-43036"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – January 23, 2018</title>
    <updated>2018-01-23T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-01-23:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Assault/Escort Map: Blizzard World&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Relive where you took your first steps in Azeroth, where you confronted the Lord of Terror, and where you spawned your first zerg rush—all of these epic memories come together on Overwatch’s newest Assault/Escort hybrid map, Blizzard World! This theme park brings the magic of Blizzard’s many worlds into one place so your most epic memories can come to life as you attack and defend the payload across Azeroth, Tristram, and the Koprulu Sector.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Blizzard World map will be disabled in Competitive Play until the start of Season 9. It will be available in Quick Play and Custom Games starting with today&#39;s patch. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cosmetics Update&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Starting now, loot boxes have been infused with over 100 cosmetics inspired by Blizzard World, Overwatch animated shorts, and more! Collect new legendary skins, including: Barbarian Zarya, Black Cat D.Va, Crusader Reinhardt, Ecopoint: Antarctica Mei, Kabuki Hanzo, and emotes such as Mercy’s Parasol, Sombra’s Marioneta, and Tracer’s Bomb Spin. Additionally, players will discover new highlight intros like Bastion’s Reconfigure, Soldier: 76’s Lights Out, Winston’s Roll, and many more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused weapon accuracy on the career profile to be displayed as 100%&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Junkrat’s Concussive Mine and Steel Trap to disappear if he placed them before using RIP-Tire&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-42936"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – January 9, 2018</title>
    <updated>2018-01-09T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2018-01-09:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overwatch League Skins Now Available&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Time to suit up, heroes! Starting now, you can directly support your favorite Overwatch League team (or teams!) by purchasing brand-new team skins to rep via the League Token system. Home-team skins are now available for all 12 teams and all 26 Heroes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Overwatch League team skins and the League Tokens, click &lt;a href=&#34;https://overwatchleague.com/en-us/news/21363697/team-skins-and-league-tokens-now-live&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;GENERAL UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Players can now watch the Overwatch League stream via the Overwatch League menu option when games are live&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Weapon accuracy is no longer increased or decreased when shooting at Genji’s Deflect or abilities that block projectiles (e.g. Winston’s Barrier Projector or Mei’s Ice Wall)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;User Interface Updates&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Zenyatta&#39;s Orb of Discord and Orb of Harmony will now display its target’s health bar&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented earned items from being displayed when a Loot Box was opened&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused a duplicate “Current Competitive Season” selection to appear in the Career Profile dropdown menu&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from being able to navigate in-game menus with the tab key&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented UI elements for Tracer’s Blink from displaying when switching between first- and third-person view in spectator mode&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the ammo count for Doomfist’s Hand Cannon from displaying when switching between first- and third-person view in spectator mode&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A.I.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the Bastion and Torbjörn bots from pathing to some areas on the first point of Eichenwalde&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the Lúcio bot to fall off the map while navigating King’s Row&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive Play&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the meters remaining to display twice when players approached the final five meters on Escort and Escort/Assault maps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Game Browser and Custom Games&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the Ultimate Duration Custom Game modification from properly adjusting Soldier: 76’s Ultimate length&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deathmatch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the Play of the Game highlight and the end-of-match screen to not display for the last player to die in the match&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Doomfist’s Rocket Punch from destroying breakable objects&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that could cause Doomfist’s Rocket Punch knock back to be inconsistent if he collided with an enemy using a movement ability (e.g. Winston’s Leap)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a latency issue that caused Doomfist’s Rocket Punch to travel through an enemy instead of dealing damage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that sometimes caused Doomfist’s Rocket Punch’s directional movement to be unpredictable&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that allowed enemies to jump over Doomfist’s Rocket Punch instead of taking damage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused enemy players hit by Doomfist’s Rocket Punch to sometimes move along the wall impacted instead of taking damage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist to move along the terrain if he impacted it with Rocket Punch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused enemies hit by Doomfist’s Rocket Punch to impact inclines instead of traveling up them&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Rocket Punch to deal wall impact damage to Mercy if she used Valkyrie&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Doomfist’s Rocket Punch to activate before intended if he was near Mei’s Ice Wall&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes caused Doomfist to fall through the ground if he used Seismic Slam on inclines&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that canceled Doomfist’s Seismic Slam when it was unable to reach the targeted location&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Junkrat’s RIP-Tire camera perspective to linger on the target after detonating&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Junkrat’s RIP-Tire to be silent to enemies while traveling on rooftops or when airborne&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes caused Snowball’s antenna to stretch out of proportion when Mei’s Beekeeper skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes caused Mercy’s Resurrect “Reviving” message to remain on the targeted player’s screen after the cast was finished&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused players targeted by Mercy’s Resurrect to no longer see their Respawn timer if her cast was interrupted by an enemy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from using Moira’s Biotic Orb if she used Fade or died while using Biotic Orb&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused Moira’s “Ultimate almost ready” voiceline to sometimes play when her Coalescence was fully charged&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Reinhardt’s Charge to knock back enemies instead of pinning them&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the visual effects of Sombra’s EMP to display when the ability was interrupted by an enemy player&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Sombra to face the incorrect direction after she teleported with Translocator&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes caused Torbjörn’s turrets to not fully heal when he used Molton Core&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Carbon Zenyatta’s in-game portrait from displaying the correct color&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug on Eichenwalde that caused the “Checkpoint Reached” voiceline to play when the payload reached its final destination&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Reaper to Shadow Step to unintended locations on Horizon Lunar Colony&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-42563"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – December 14, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-12-14T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2017-12-14:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused the game client to crash when certain visual effects were displayed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive Play&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug in Competitive Play that sometimes caused incorrect time adjustments between subsequent rounds on hybrid maps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that sometimes caused Roadhog’s Chain Hook to miss targets from certain angles and distances&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Torbjörn’s Forge Hammer from upgrading his turret when used at certain angles and distances&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-42210"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>