<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Overwatch PC Updates</title>
  <id>https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
  <updated>2017-11-30T16:59:36-08:00</updated>
  <subtitle>Patch notes and updates for Overwatch</subtitle>
  <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/"></link>
  <author>
    <name>Blizzard</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – November 30, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-11-30T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2017-11-30:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size:22px;&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moira&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Changed Moira’s ultimate ability name from Fusión to Coalescencia in Latin American Spanish (esMX)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added four new voice lines when Moira says her ultimate ability name in Latin American Spanish (esMX)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size:22px;&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COMPETITIVE PLAY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Made improvements to matchmaking that will decrease the range of Skill Rating between players on the same team&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;This change will help players get placed with allies and against opponents of a similar skill level, which should lead to more satisfying games.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size:22px;&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused the main menu to be unusable for certain players&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Moira’s Biotic Orb to pass through terrain and structures unintentionally&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-41773"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – November 16, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-11-16T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2017-11-16:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Hero: Moira (Support):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wielding both regenerative and degenerative technologies at her fingertips, &lt;strong&gt;Moira&lt;/strong&gt; O’Deorain is Talon’s ambitious geneticist who seeks the knowledge to rewrite the building blocks of human life by any means necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moira’s cutting-edge capabilities make her a mobile healer and damage dealer capable of adapting to any situation. Her main attack is &lt;strong&gt;Biotic Grasp&lt;/strong&gt;, which she can use to either heal allies or sap an enemy’s life force. Biotic Grasp’s primary fire sprays a cone of energy that heals all teammates within range, draining biotic energy while active, which will replenish slowly over time. Her alternate fire is a beam that tethers to enemies, dealing damage and siphoning health. Draining her foes’ health regenerates Moira’s biotic energy even faster, allowing more healing for her allies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Her &lt;strong&gt;Biotic Orb&lt;/strong&gt; ability launches a sphere of energy that bounces around the battlefield, healing nearby allies or damaging enemies until it dissipates. &lt;strong&gt;Fade&lt;/strong&gt; enables Moira to disappear out of sight and sprint through the shadows, and makes her invulnerable for its duration. When Moira’s ultimate is ready to be unleashed, she can cast &lt;strong&gt;Coalescence&lt;/strong&gt;—a powerful, long-range beam of chaotic energy that pierces through barriers to heal allies or damage enemies in its path.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;centered&#34; style=&#34;margin-bottom:25px;&#34;&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/8tLopqeL9s8?theme=light&amp;amp;color=white&amp;amp;cc_load_policy=1&amp;amp;HD=1&amp;amp;rel=0&amp;amp;showinfo=0&#34; style=&#34;border-bottom:1px solid lightgray;&#34; width=&#34;560&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Moira, click &lt;a href=&#34;https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/heroes/moira/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;As with all new heroes, please note that Moira’s release in Competitive Play will be delayed by one week.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;GENERAL UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Clicking the &#34;leave game as group&#34; checkbox will now remember your selection for future matches&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Arcade&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;One of the arcade slots will now change on a daily basis to include a variety of game modes such as Limited Duel, Low Gravity, and Capture the Flag&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ana&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Biotic Rifle&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Damage increased from 60 to 70&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ana has been outshined by other support heroes lately. Boosting her damage will help her defend herself and make her more threatening to the enemy team.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lúcio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lúcio now has an effect above his head to indicate which song he&#39;s playing in spectator mode&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mercy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Caduceus Staff&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Increased visual readability of Mercy&#39;s healing and damage boosting beams&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Resurrect&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cast time increased from 0 seconds to 1.75 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mercy&#39;s movement speed is now reduced by 75% while casting&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Can now be interrupted when Mercy is knocked back, stunned, or hacked&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Valkyrie&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;While active, Resurrect no longer has a cast time&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;While active, casting Resurrect does not reduce Mercy&#39;s movement speed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comment: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;We feel that Mercy’s recent rework has been successful, but her Resurrect ability still feels too strong and frustrating to play against. Now that it has a cast time, enemies are more able to counter the ability. However, Resurrect will cast instantly when Valkyrie is active. This should make her feel powerful when she transforms on the battlefield.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winston&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Barrier Projector&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now displays a health bar&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comment: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;This change will help both Winston&#39;s allies and enemies know how much more damage his shield can absorb from oncoming attacks.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;COMPETITIVE PLAY&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Grandmaster players can now only group up with other players within 250 Skill Rating&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comment: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;We have tightened the Skill Rating range that Grandmaster players can group up with from 500 SR down to 250 SR. This is to ensure our highest ranked players are playing with equally skilled people, which should lead to more satisfying games.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;USER INTERFACE&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Made several visual adjustments to revamp the spectator mode HUD including an improved spectator mode UI, a new unit frame style, and an animated ultimate indicator&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented player portrait borders from loading in the Hero Select screen or on the Match Status screen&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented players from adding spectators to a Deathmatch game from within the Custom Game lobby&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A.I.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented bots from respawning when they were moved to a different slot or team within the Custom Game lobby&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the Sombra bot from hacking health packs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that affected the Bastion bot’s movement when defending Point A on Eichenwalde&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented bots from defending Point A on certain maps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Ana’s sidearm to emit a bright light when viewed in the Hero Gallery&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented Ganymede from making appropriate roadrunner noises when Bastion’s Dune Buggy skin was equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Mercy’s ultimate icon from displaying correctly when hacked by Sombra&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue causing Roadhog’s Chain Hook to latch on to enemy players for longer than intended&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an animation bug that caused Widowmaker’s knees to snap together when jumping&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused the toy robot in Zarya’s Mystery Gift emote to inflate when she tore it apart&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented Junkrat’s RIP-Tire from casting properly while jumping&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the incorrect stage of the map (e.g. Sanctum on Nepal) to be displayed during the hero selection phase when playing on Nepal and Lijiang Tower&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the progress bar from displaying briefly when players reached checkpoints on Escort and Escort/Assault maps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented the targeting UI on Doomfist’s Seismic Slam from functioning correctly when aiming at the spinning turbine blade near the last point of Junkertown&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused some objects to uncharacteristically fly across the room when shot on Horizon Lunar Colony&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-41350"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – October 17, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-10-17T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2017-10-17:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;GENERAL UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Players can now set their social status to Online, Away, Busy, or Appear Offline (Note: appearing offline does not prevent friends from seeing you if you are placed into the same match). This option can be found under the social menu&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lúcio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Wall Ride&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The speed boost that Lúcio receives after completing a wall ride has been increased by 65%&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;A recent bug fix slowed Lúcio’s Wall Ride. This change compensates for the reduced speed.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mercy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Guardian Angel&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Players can now glide past a targeted ally using the jump key&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cooldown no longer resets when Resurrect is activated&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Valkyrie&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No longer resets or reduces Resurrection’s cooldown&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now gives players a bonus resurrection charge&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comment: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Valkyrie no longer resets or reduces Resurrect’s cooldown. Instead, it now provides an extra &#39;charge,&#39; allowing you to revive an ally even if it is still on cooldown. If the bonus charge hasn’t been spent when Valkyrie ends, it will be removed.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This method makes Resurrect more flexible when used with Valkyrie. For example, in the past if you wanted to resurrect two teammates, you had to revive the first target, then activate Valkyrie (causing the Resurrect’s cooldown to reset), and then revive the other target. With this change, you can now activate Valkyrie and fly in quickly to resurrect both targets instantly.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;However, this still reduces the overall number of Resurrects that Mercy can provide, since Valkyrie no longer reduces its cooldown.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zenyatta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added a number of additional voicelines for Cultist Zenyatta&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug preventing Mercy’s momentum from slowing down correctly when Guardian Angel was canceled&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug preventing the visual effects on Sombra’s Pumpkinette victory pose from displaying correctly&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-40570"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – October 10, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-10-10T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2017-10-10:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC, PlayStation 4, and Xbox One. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Seasonal Event: Overwatch Halloween Terror 2017&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The fright for the future returns!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For a limited time, explore the haunted streets of Eichenwalde and Hollywood, expand your collection of spooky seasonal cosmetics, and team up to fight evil incarnate once more in not one, but two Junkenstein&#39;s Revenge-themed brawls! We&#39;re also re-opening our crypt so players can unlock their favorite Halloween-themed items from last year along with over 50 new tantalizing treats, including legendary skins like Corsair Ana, Van Helsing McCree, Dragon Symmetra, Cultist Zenyatta, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Overwatch Halloween Terror, &lt;a href=&#34;http://blizz.ly/OHT2017&#34;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Epic Skin: BlizzCon 2017 Winston&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Through the power of science, Winston has traveled with his trusty jump pack from his base in Gibraltar all the way to Anaheim, California for BlizzCon 2017. We’ve given him a special souvenir to mark the curious occasion and he’d like to share it with you. Starting today, this new skin is available in-game for all BlizzCon Virtual Ticket holders—&lt;a href=&#34;https://blizzcon.com/en-us/event-info/tickets/virtual&#34;&gt;click here to learn more&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;GENERAL UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overwatch Halloween Terror Victory Pose Updates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ve made a few changes to this year&#39;s selection of seasonal victory poses. To learn more about this change, &lt;a href=&#34;https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20759338520#1&#34;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;HERO UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ultimate charge is now immediately expended when a hero&#39;s ultimate ability is activated, instead of depleting over a short period of time&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;One of the most common pieces of feedback we receive revolves around the way Overwatch handles ultimate interruptions. Players often feel frustrated when they’re able to prevent an enemy from using an ultimate, only to see that same enemy use it again immediately after respawning&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Until now, many ultimates drained the meter quickly over time, instead of instantly setting the meter to zero when the button was pressed. We originally designed it this way to ensure that players had the chance to use (at the very least) a little of their ultimate every time. However, we now feel that it causes too much frustration without adding many benefits.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;With this patch, ultimate abilities will instantly set a hero’s meter to zero when the button is pressed, which means stopping an enemy ultimate at any point after it’s activated will ensure that it has been spent.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Another piece of feedback we often hear is that it’s difficult to understand which abilities are interruptible and which are not. For clarity, most of Overwatch’s ultimates fall into three basic categories: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Transformation Ultimates&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;:&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;&#x9;These add significant passive benefits to your heroes, while allowing the use of weapons and abilities.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;&lt;u&gt;Ultimates in this category&lt;/u&gt;: Bastion&#39;s Configuration: Tank, Genji&#39;s Dragonblade, Mercy&#39;s Valkyrie, Soldier: 76&#39;s Tactical Visor, Torbjörn&#39;s Molten Core, and Widowmaker&#39;s Infra-Sight.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;&#x9; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Channeled Ultimates&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;: These force your hero into a new mode and render your other abilities unusable while active. In most cases, these abilities can be interrupted at any point to cancel them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;Ultimates in this category&lt;/u&gt;: Doomfist’s Meteor Strike, McCree&#39;s Deadeye, Pharah’s Barrage, Reaper’s Death Blossom, Roadhog’s Whole Hog, and Zenyatta&#39;s Transcendence (though, Zenyatta’s ultimate renders him immune to interruptions).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;&#x9; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cast-Time Ultimates&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;: These abilities require a small window of time to pass before they become effective. If they’re interrupted during this window, they are canceled.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;Ultimates in this category&lt;/u&gt;: Ana&#39;s Nano Boost, D.Va’s Call Mech and Self-Destruct, Hanzo&#39;s Dragonstrike, Junkrat&#39;s Rip-Tire, Lúcio’s Sound Barrier, Mei&#39;s Blizzard, Orisa&#39;s Supercharger, Reinhardt&#39;s Earthshatter, Sombra&#39;s EMP, Symmetra&#39;s Shield Generator and Teleporter, Tracer&#39;s Pulse Bomb, and Zarya&#39;s Graviton Surge. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Most abilities fit neatly within these categories but we did make some changes to outliers such as Genji&#39;s Dragonblade and Orisa&#39;s Supercharger to make them more consistent. Additionally, any ultimate that can be interrupted by a stun (Channeled ultimates and Cast-Time ultimates) can now be interrupted by Sombra’s Hack as well. Overall these changes should make it much easier to understand the ultimate mechanics and how they interact in combat.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;D.Va&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Boosters&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;An option to manually hold down D.Va’s boosters rather than toggling them has been added under Options &amp;gt; Controls &amp;gt; D.Va&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Genji&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dragonblade&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No longer interrupted when Genji is stunned or hacked&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;See the above developer comment on ultimate interruptions&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Orisa&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Supercharger&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Can now be interrupted when Orisa is stunned or hacked&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;See the above developer comment on ultimate interruptions&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sombra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hack&#xA;&#x9;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now interrupts the following ultimate abilities during their cast time: Ana&#39;s Nano Boost, Orisa&#39;s Supercharger, Mei&#39;s Blizzard, Reinhardt&#39;s Earthshatter, and D.Va&#39;s Call Mech&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;See the above developer comment on ultimate interruptions&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;USER INTERFACE UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assault Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;When capturing an objective, the progress bar is now broken into three segments that will fill in with the team’s color that is capturing it (as each segment fills, it will trigger an animation and audio cue)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The number of defenders currently on the objective will now be displayed in addition to the number of attackers, just below the progress bar&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed muted players to become unmuted after leaving and rejoining the same match&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A.I.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused bots to get trapped in a movement loop after taking the tunnel under the capture point in the University section of Oasis&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive Play&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused matches to end in a draw when both teams won their first attacking rounds in overtime on Hanamura, Horizon Lunar Colony, Temple of Anubis, and Volskaya Industries&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Custom Games and Game Browser&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the Capture Speed Modifier setting from being applied in custom games&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented D.Va’s Projectile Speed slider from appearing in Custom Game settings&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented D.Va’s Micro Missles from producing rumble feedback when using a controller with vibration enabled&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Lúcio’s soccer ball to fly off in the wrong direction when activating his Juggle emote at 30 FPS&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Mercy to maintain forward momentum after canceling Guardian Angel mid-flight&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that could cause heroes to respawn as a different hero after being resurrected by Mercy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused Roadhog’s chest to deflate when his Tuckered Out emote was activated while the Mako or Sharkbait skins were equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the sound effects on Symmetra’s turrets from being heard by teammates&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Torbjörn’s weapon-draw animation from being played when turret placement was canceled&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug on Junkertown that allowed some heroes to get stuck behind a barrel near the final point&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug on King’s Row that caused a dark box to appear if you stared into the robot city for too long&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Sombra to reach unintended locations on Volskaya Industries&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug affecting Ilios, Lijang Tower, Nepal, and Oasis that prevented overtime progress from resetting when the point had been flipped after both teams’ progress bars reached 99%&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that could cause Widowmaker’s scoped overlay to appear while spectating her from third person view&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-40407"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Overwatch Patch Notes – September 21, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-09-21T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>tag:playoverwatch.com,2017-09-21:/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;General Discussion&lt;/a&gt; forum&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href=&#34;http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please note that these changes will be rolled into a larger patch for PlayStation 4 and Xbox One at a later date.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;GENERAL UPDATES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The credit that Mercy’s Resurrect contributes toward her on-fire meter has been adjusted to account for the recent changes in its functionality&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Arcade&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hanamura, Horizon Lunar Colony, Temple of Anubis, and Volskaya Industries have been removed from the Deathmatch and Team Deathmatch map rotation, but can still be selected in Custom Games&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User Interface&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Made several adjustments to the spectator camera to improve the viewing experience&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused the audio from Junkertown’s front gate to play when previewing and opening Loot Boxes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented the stagger and knockdown VO from canceling active voice lines&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed an incorrect voice line to play when firing D.Va&#39;s Micro Missiles&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused the spectator camera to lose track of heroes and player-controlled objects (e.g. Junkrat’s RIP-Tire)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented Genji and Mercy’s ultimate voice lines from functioning properly when the Oni or Winged Victory skins were equipped&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused sound effects to continuously repeat when using a beam weapon (e.g. Zarya&#39;s Particle Cannon) to destroy the motorcycle in the attackers&#39; spawn room on Junkertown&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that activated audio cues that are typically associated with enemy hits when shooting the motorcycle on Junkertown&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</content>
    <link href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/game/patch-notes/pc/#patch-39974"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Overwatch PC Team</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>