<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Overwatch PC Updates</title>
  <id>https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/21446648/</id>
  <updated>2017-04-11T12:01:08-07:00</updated>
  <subtitle>Patch notes and updates for Overwatch</subtitle>
  <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/21446648/"></link>
  <author>
    <name>Blizzard</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>[ALL] Overwatch Patch Notes – April 11, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-04-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2017-04-11:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20753818008</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC, PlayStation 4, and Xbox One. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussionforum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. JUMP TO SECTION: Patch Highlights General Hero Updates Bug Fixes</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20753818008"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[PC] Overwatch Patch Notes – March 28, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-03-28T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2017-03-28:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20753775700</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. BUG FIXES General Fixed a bug that prevented the Damage Amplified stat from appearing in the scoreboard at the end of a game Heroes Fixed a bug to prevent Orisa from deploying her Supercharger inside of the payload Fixed a bug that prevented Sombra’s “BOOP” voice line from playing Orisa’s movement now slows slightly while firing in midair Developer Comments: Much like D.Va’s Fusion Cannons, Orisa’s Fusion Driver is intended to slow her movement while she is firing. However, unlike D.Va, there was an issue that prevented this slow from working while firing from the air.</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20753775700"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[ALL] Overwatch Patch Notes – March 21, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-03-21T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2017-03-21:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20753508356</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC, PlayStation 4, and Xbox One. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. JUMP TO SECTION: Patch Highlights General Updates Hero Updates Bug Fixes</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20753508356"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[ALL] Overwatch Patch Notes – March 8, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-03-08T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2017-03-08:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20753436342</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC, PlayStation 4, and Xbox One. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. Please note that changes marked as [Console Only] have already been implemented on PC in a previous patch. GENERAL Arcade [Console Only] 1v1 Mystery Duel game mode is now available in the Arcade Custom Games Players can no longer gain EXP from skirmishes in custom games AFK detection has been added to skirmishes in custom games</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20753436342"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[PC] Overwatch Patch Notes – March 3, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-03-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2017-03-03:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20753626069</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. Please note that these changes will be rolled into a larger patch for PlayStation 4 and Xbox One at a later date. HERO UPDATES: General The total damage reduction that a hero can receive while buffed (e.g. from Ana&#39;s Nano Boost and Orisa&#39;s Fortify) has been capped at 50% (formerly 70%) Bastion Ironclad Bastion now takes 20% less damage while in Configuration: Sentry or Tank (formerly 35%) Developer Comments: After introducing the new Ironclad passive ability in the last patch, Bastion felt a little too difficult to deal with. This reduction maintains his survivability while he’s transformed, but he shouldn’t feel so overbearing to enemies. Zarya Particle Barrier No longer protects Zarya from knockback Projected Barrier No longer protects allies from knockback Developer Comments: This change is actually reverting an attempted bug fix from a previous patch. Now, Zarya’s barriers no longer protect players who are hit by a knockback effect that pierces the shield. This change does not affect knockback abilities that occur outside the barriers. For example, if Zarya has a barrier on herself and is hit by one of Pharah’s concussive blasts, she won’t be affected, because the barrier blocked the effect. However, if Winston uses his ultimate and starts to swing at Zarya, it will now knock her back even if a protective barrier is active, since melee attacks pierce barriers. BUG FIXES Arcade Fixed an issue preventing heroes in 1v1 Mystery Duel from being shuffled correctly Competitive Fixed an issue preventing players from loading the Season 1 and 2 leaderboards Heroes Fixed an issue preventing D.Va’s Defense Matrix from properly blocking enemy fire that has passed through another enemy hero Fixed an issue preventing Winston’s hitbox from lining up with his pose while crouched</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20753626069"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[ALL] Overwatch Patch Notes – February 28, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-02-28T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2017-02-28:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20753535162</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC, PlayStation 4, and Xbox One. Read below to learn about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. JUMP TO SECTION: Patch Highlights Hero Updates Competitive Play Map Balance Changes Bug Fixes</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20753535162"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[PC] Overwatch Patch Notes – February 8, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-02-08T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2017-02-08:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20753236961</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. BUG FIXES: General Fixed an issue that prevented the Year of the Rooster version of Lijang Tower from being playable in Quick Play and Competitive Play</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20753236961"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[PC] Overwatch Patch Notes – January 31, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-01-31T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2017-01-31:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20753275781</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. Please note that these changes will be rolled into a larger patch for PlayStation 4 and Xbox One at a later date. BUG FIXES: General Fixed a bug that allowed the flag to get stuck outside the standard gameplay boundaries in Capture the Rooster Fixed a bug that allowed Competitive Matches to continue indefinitely Fixed a bug that allowed Tracer and Mei to reach unintended locations outside the standard gameplay boundaries on several maps Fixed a bug preventing Reinhardt’s shield from displaying cracks at low health when the Wujing skin was equipped</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20753275781"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[ALL] Overwatch Patch Notes – January 24, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-01-24T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2017-01-24:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20752795395</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC, PlayStation 4, and Xbox One. Read below to learn about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. JUMP TO SECTION: Patch Highlights General Updates Hero Balance Updates Bug Fixes</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20752795395"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[PC] Overwatch Patch Notes – January 12, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-01-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2017-01-12:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20752529816</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. PATCH HIGHLIGHTS New Feature: Blizzard Checkout Purchasing Loot Boxes has never been easier. Our streamlined system gives players access more payment options from directly within the Overwatch client. GENERAL UPDATES General Decreased the volume of passing cars on the Oasis background in the Hero Gallery BUG FIXES Heroes Fixed a bug that was allowing Mercy to resurrect players that had fallen off the map to their death Maps Fixed a bug to prevent the garden point on Oasis from being contested/captured from the second-floor walkway above it Fixed a bug that allowed Sombra to reach unintended locations on several maps</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20752529816"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[ALL] Overwatch Patch Notes – January 3, 2017</title>
    <updated>2017-01-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2017-01-03:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20752488691</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC, PlayStation 4, and Xbox One. Read below to learn about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. PATCH HIGHLIGHTS New Control Map: Oasis Oasis is one of the world&#39;s most advanced cities, a shining jewel rising from the Arabian Desert. A monument to human ingenuity and invention, researchers and academics from around the region came together to found a city dedicated to scientific progress without restraints. The city and its inhabitants are governed by the Ministries, a collection of brilliant minds who possess many secrets, which have attracted the interest of powerful organizations from around the world.</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20752488691"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[PC] Overwatch Patch Notes – December 20, 2016</title>
    <updated>2016-12-20T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2016-12-20:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20752466918</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. Please note that these changes will be rolled into a larger patch for PlayStation 4 and Xbox One at a later date. BUG FIXES: General Mouse 4 no longer controls backwards menu navigation, preventing conflicts with other functions that might be bound to that button Fixed a bug preventing audio from mixing correctly on the main menu screen Competitive Play Fixed a bug that sometimes allowed Symmetra to place Teleporters and Shield Generators inside her team’s spawn room in a competitive match Heroes Fixed a bug that allowed Sombra to permanently hack a health pack</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20752466918"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[ALL] Overwatch Patch Notes – December 13, 2016</title>
    <updated>2016-12-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2016-12-13:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20752545497</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC, PlayStation 4, and Xbox One. Read below to learn about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. JUMP TO SECTION: Patch Highlights General Updates Hero Balance Updates Bug Fixes</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20752545497"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[PC] Overwatch Patch Notes – November 30, 2016</title>
    <updated>2016-11-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2016-11-30:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20752217167</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. Please note that these changes will be rolled into a larger patch for PlayStation 4 and Xbox One at a later date. BUG FIXES: Arcade Fixed a bug that prevented Ana from being selected in 1v1 matches Heroes Fixed a bug that allowed Mercy to receive Ultimate charge when using her Cadueus Staff to increase teammates’ damage when they’re not damaging enemies Fixed a bug preventing Reinhardt from deactivating his Barrier Field after being hacked by Sombra Fixed a bug preventing Sombra’s Hack from cancelling Soldier: 76’s Sprint ability Sombra no longer receives credit toward her on-fire meter when her EMP ultimate hits Symmetra’s turrets When multiple Sombras attempt to hack a health pack, the player that initialized the hack first will now control it Fixed a bug preventing Sombra from seeing practice bots, whose health has fallen below 50%, through the walls on the Practice Range Fixed a bug preventing Sombra’s reticle from consistently expanding while firing her machine pistol</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20752217167"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[PC] Overwatch Patch Notes – November 16, 2016</title>
    <updated>2016-11-16T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2016-11-16:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20752215318</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. Please note that these changes will be rolled into a larger patch for PlayStation 4 and Xbox One at a later date. BUG FIXES: General Fixed an issue which prevented players from saving their Graphics Quality settings when attempting to use the “Epic” preference (Options &gt; Video) Fixed a bug that allowed healers to gain Ultimate charge more quickly than intended</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20752215318"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[ALL] Overwatch Patch Notes – November 15, 2016</title>
    <updated>2016-11-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2016-11-15:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20752015856</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC, PlayStation 4, and Xbox One. Read below to learn about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. JUMP TO SECTION: Patch Highlights General Updates Hero Balance Updates User Interface Updates Bug Fixes</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20752015856"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[PC] Overwatch Patch Notes – October 20, 2016</title>
    <updated>2016-10-20T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2016-10-20:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20749777650</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. Please note that these changes will be rolled into a larger patch for PlayStation 4 and Xbox One at a later date. BUG FIXES: Maps Fixed a bug that caused players to get stuck on the loading screen when entering Ilios and Lijiang Tower</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20749777650"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[PC] Overwatch Patch Notes – October 19, 2016</title>
    <updated>2016-10-19T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2016-10-19:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20749856850</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. Please note that these changes will be rolled into a larger patch for PlayStation 4 and Xbox One at a later date. BUG FIXES: General Fixed an issue causing the default Overwatch spray to override a player’s chosen spray when watching a Play of the Game or Highlight Fixed an issue causing players to frequently disconnect while viewing Highlights Fixed a bug preventing the appropriate music from playing after a loss on the Junkenstein&#39;s Revenge Brawl Gameplay Fixed a bug causing multiple issues when displaying data on the leaderboards Heroes Fixed an issue preventing Ana’s Nano Boost callouts from being heard by the enemy team Fixed a bug preventing players from receiving credit toward the Healing Done commendation when healing D.Va’s mech Fixed a graphical issue that was preventing the liquid in Mei’s Endothermic Blaster from appearing Fixed a bug causing Reinhardt’s Charge to unexpectedly stop when crossing certain thresholds (e.g. when exiting a dropship) Increased the volume of Roadhog’s “Want some candy” voice line Map Fixed a bug on Eichenwalde that caused some textures to stretch across the map for some players</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20749856850"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[ALL] Overwatch Patch Notes – October 11, 2016</title>
    <updated>2016-10-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2016-10-11:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20749875377</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. JUMP TO SECTION: Patch Highlights General Updates Hero Balance Updates User Interface Updates Bug Fixes</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20749875377"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[PC] Overwatch Patch Notes – September 30, 2016</title>
    <updated>2016-09-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2016-09-30:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20749277515</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. Please note that these changes will be rolled into a larger patch for PlayStation 4 and Xbox One at a later date. BUG FIXES: Fixed an issue that was preventing some players from being able to rejoin a match after being disconnected Slightly extended the amount of time that players have to rejoin an in-progress match when disconnected</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20749277515"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[PC] Overwatch Patch Notes – September 23, 2016</title>
    <updated>2016-09-23T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2016-09-23:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20749355673</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. Please note that these changes will be rolled into a larger patch for PlayStation 4 and Xbox One at a later date. BUG FIXES: Fixed an issue that was incorrectly displaying a top 500 icon for certain players, even though they had not yet broken into the top 500</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20749355673"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[ALL] Overwatch Patch Notes – September 13, 2016</title>
    <updated>2016-09-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2016-09-13:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20749157415</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC, PlayStation 4, and Xbox One. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. GENERAL UPDATES General Players should now see fewer Plays of the Game featuring Mercy’s Resurrection ability Increased payload speed on Eichenwalde USER INTERFACE UPDATES General A new Competitive Tier legend has been added to the Competitive Play info screen A new Match Complete splash screen has replaced the former Round Complete splash screen in competitive matches BUG FIXES General Fixed a bug which prevented the Triple Kill announcement from being played after a kill streak of 3 or more Fixed several issues causing some players obtain a skill rating that&#39;s higher than their actual rating Note: A very small number of people were affected by these issues, but those who were affected will have their skill rating adjusted appropriately Heroes Fixed a bug causing the wrong arrow to be shown on Hanzo&#39;s bow, or disappear entirely (the correct arrow would still be fired) Fixed a bug preventing Junkrat’s RIP-Tire from receiving credit for kills, achievements, and other stats Maps Fixed a bug allowing Reaper to Shadow Step to unintended locations on Hollywood</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20749157415"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Josh Engen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[PC] Overwatch Patch Notes – August 16, 2016</title>
    <updated>2016-08-16T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2016-08-16:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20748545700</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. Please note that these changes will be rolled into a larger patch for PlayStation 4 and Xbox One at a later date. BUG FIXES: Fixed a bug that was blocking spectator cameras from passing through some doors and force fields</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20748545700"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Lylirra</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[PC] Overwatch Patch Notes – August 9, 2016</title>
    <updated>2016-08-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2016-08-09:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20748354637</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. Please note that many of these changes will be rolled into a larger patch for PlayStation 4 and Xbox One at a later date. MAP BALANCE UPDATES Respawn time for defenders has been standardized to 10 seconds on all maps Payload speed has been slightly reduced on Watchpoint: Gibraltar BUG FIXES General Fixed a bug causing incomplete character models to load on the Hero Selection screen Fixed a number of bugs causing various crashes and instability issues Competitive Play Fixed a bug that prevented user interface elements from displaying in some languages Fixed a bug that caused the placement matches screen to display when some players would disconnect and rejoin a match Maps Estádio das Rãs Fixed a bug that allowed players to spawn as heroes other than Lúcio Nepal Fixed an issue which allowed players to get stuck outside the normal boundaries of the map Temple of Anubis Fixed a bug causing a portion of the city wall to display incorrectly on all graphics settings</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20748354637"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Lylirra</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[ALL] Overwatch Patch Notes – August 2, 2016</title>
    <updated>2016-08-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2016-08-02:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20747925082</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on PC, PlayStation 4, and Xbox One. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. JUMP TO SECTION: All Platforms Console-Specific Changes Important: If you are experiencing technical issues with the patching process, connecting to Battle.net after installing the patch, or errors while playing a newly-patched game, please visit our support site, post in the Technical Support forum, or contact @BlizzardCS for assistance.</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20747925082"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Lylirra</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>[PC] Overwatch Patch Notes – July 26, 2016</title>
    <updated>2016-07-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>tag:us.battle.net,2016-07-26:/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20747615932</id>
    <content type="html">A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes. To share your feedback, please post in the General Discussion forum. For a list of known issues, visit our Bug Report forum. For troubleshooting assistance, visit our Technical Support forum. Please note that many of these changes will be rolled into a larger patch for PlayStation 4 and Xbox One at a later date. HERO BALANCE UPDATES Ana Biotic Rifle Rate of fire increased by 20% Magazine size increased from 8 to 10 Developer Comments: While Ana has been very well received, she was showing to be a little bit weaker overall. In addition to helping her feel better to play, these changes should also increase her healing and damage output. McCree Peacemaker Primary Fire Damage falloff range decreased by 10 meters Damage falloff amount is unchanged As a result, even with this change, McCree’s effective range is still higher than it was at launch Alternate Fire Rate of fire increased by 15% Flashbang Recovery time (i.e. the amount of time before McCree can fire again) decreased from 0.5 seconds to 0.35 seconds Developer Comments: McCree’s latest range increase helped him quite a bit, but it was a bit too much in the right hands. This change weakens his long range damage somewhat, but still keeps it stronger than it has been in the recent past. The other changes combine to allow him to land more alternate fire shots on targets that he has hit with Flashbang. BUG FIXES Heroes Targets of Ana’s Sleep Dart will no longer instantly recover when damaged (recovery time is now 0.5 seconds) User Interface Fixed UI compatibility issues for ATI cards Fixed a bug that would sometimes cause Lúcio, Mei, and other models to only partially render (or disappear)</content>
    <link href="https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20747615932"></link>
    <author>
      <name>Lylirra</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
